[♪♪♪]
Ja, all this is under control.
$150 million,
and my dope is on the way.
Today is gonna be a good day.
We are 25 degrees north,
84 degrees west.
The cargo's being dropped.
[BEEPING]
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
[BEEP]
Good.
Do you want to see his gun?
Yeah.
Bang. Bang.
[GUNSHOT]
Sorry, Johnny.
Fucking bitches.
Infrared's picking up a live one
on the water.
This is Air Force
Stallion C-14 to Coast Guard.
We're picking up
a fast-moving contact
heading 3-5-0
toward South Florida.
Captain, Air Force Stallion
has a contact at 1-8-0
closing fast.
This is Coast Guard
cutter Valiant.
Request to know your intentions
at this time.
Vessel off our port bow,
this is U.S. Coast Guard.
Intercept is 1-8-0,
speed 17 knots.
Make it so, chief.
Scramble the helo.
Vessel off our port bow,
vessel off our port bow.
This is U.S. Coast Guard,
U.S. Coast Guard.
Request to know your intentions
at this time.
Incoming.
Valiant, Valiant, Valiant,
This is Coast Guard 6-0-0-3.
Negative contact with target.
Over.
Captain, we've lost target.
Here's your delivery
and payment.
Is it done?
Cargo is on Dixie 7.
Okay.
All right, TNT,
for the millionth time,
listen up.
Since 9-11, we've gone hi-tech
over the water,
so the dope runners
have gone low.
Our source says
the biggest X shipment on record
is coming in tonight,
and we want to know
who's behind it.
Hopefully in a few hours,
we'll have our answer.
We're going to hit them
from three directions:
We're going with a water team,
vehicle assault,
and we got guys on foot.
We cannot make a move
until our UCs
have ID'd the drugs
and called us in.
No call, we back away.
And these guys
we're going after,
they got a lot of firepower,
and they hate the law,
so eyes open out there.
Bravo's on the move.
Heads up. Here comes the drop.
Fuck. My lens is flaring.
I can't see shit.
Brothers! Gather 'round!
Hey.
Why didn't you tell me
there was a rally tonight?
Who's looking?
Take that shit.
I'm out of here.
Shit.
White power!
Blue power, motherfuckers.
Miami PD.
Aw, damn. It's the Negroes.
Casper, drop the bag.
Alpha leader,
bring them in.
♪ Bad boys, bad boys
What you gonna do? ♪
♪ What you gonna do
When we come for you? ♪
♪ ...nax mez nose na-hey ♪
Dude, you gotta learn the words.
We usually only do the chorus.
Alpha leader, hit it. Br...
Repeat your transmission.
Alpha leader to Bravo Four,
please continue relay.
Where's backup?
Alpha leader,
bring them in.
Hit it.
Mike, I'm only getting static.
All I'm getting is static.
These radios are fucked.
Something funny? Something
funny?
Mike, where are they?
Got you, nigger.
Whoo!
[CLICK]
Looks like we got us
a situation here.
You ain't gonna
shoot, nigger.
Just 'cause you got that gun
to my partner's head,
you're thinking I ain't gonna
splatter your shit all over?
That's what I'm thinking.
See, what you don't understand
is my partner came here tonight
prepared to die.
Hell...Hell, no!
Incinerating trash like you.
Ready to die,
ain't you, Marcus?
The fuck I want to do that for?
Scared, ain't you, boy?
A, You can
put that gun down,
tell me who's bringing
this shit in,
and maybe I'll just
pop one in your shoulder,
or B, you can keep acting
all Brody,
and I'm going to plant one
in your chest...
Or C, you know, take the time
to talk a minute...
you know,
de-escalate the situation.
You see, that's some
new spiritual bullshit
my partner's on.
Me?
I actually prefer
shooting motherfuckers.
A lot of movement going on.
Can't see the UCs.
I think something's
going down.
Don't move yet.
Mike, the man
has a gun to my head.
I bet he'll put it down
if I put a hollow point
in his eye.
Your partner's
a cocky nigger.
Damn. Now, was that necessary,
sir?
See?
How come he can't just be a cop?
He got to be a nigga too?
I'm gonna go ahead
and hot this fool.
Mike, look, calm down.
Calm down? I'm calm.
I'm calm! Hey! Whoa! Whoa!
I am way too unstable
for that bullshit.
Stop all the goddamn
movement!
Everybody stop moving!
We can't let you all go,
but look, this shit'll
get worked out in court.
We got our rights.
Why don't you
exercise your right
to shut the fuck up?
I'm all right.
I'm just going
to give you a warning, okay?
That's the best I can fucking do
for all of youse!
Okay? He's crazy.
You got three seconds
to put your gun down, sir.
He has emotional
anger issue problems!
One.
He goes to bed early
for this shit!
Just to wake up to pop one
in a motherfucker!
Two!
Mike, no!
Gun!
Rock 'n' roll! Let's go!
Kill them cops!
Marcus!
Go! Go! Go! Go! Come on, go!
Get down!
Drop the...!
I didn't do shit!
Get your hands up.
The radios were fucked up.
Get some medics over here.
You guys okay?
Yeah, we're fine.
What you mean, "we"?
Motherfucker shot me
in the ass, man.
Who shot you in the ass?
Who? That "who" would be you.
Me? I shot you?
Yeah.
I mean, I was shooting.
Yeah, I did a lot of shooting,
but I ain't saying
I shot you in the ass.
I mean, I ain't saying
I didn't shoot you...
but, damn! Somebody
shot you in the ass.
Tell me about it.
Yo, man,
how's it feel?
It's hot, man.
I can smell my ass burning.
Yo, Mike, why don't you just
give it a little kiss, man,
you know,
so it'll feel better?
Hey, just pretend like
we're not even here, man.
Hey, isn't Ricky Martin
having a concert?
Get the fuck on.
You always gotta
go racial, man.
It's sad, man.
I think it's cool, man.
It hit the meat.
It ain't nowhere
near the hole.
Two lousy bags?
What ever happened to
the biggest shipment of ecstasy
to ever come out of Amsterdam?
Let me worry about
my snitch, all right?
It's a lot of cop work
for nothing!
Take your ass
home somewhere.
Tonight la policia
jacked my mules.
Who in this room
full of my manos
can tell me how those jackals
knew where to bite Johnny Tapia?
Speak up, cousins.
You're lucky they did not
find my drugs on Dixie 7.
Change the boat schedule.
We can't change it
now, Johnny.
We got a shipment Thursday.
Change it after.
Just keep them guessing.
You know, unlike you,
my daddy didn't leave
me no trust fund.
I got real-world shit
to deal with, Mike.
I'm not in it
for the thrills.
Same old shit, different day.
All right, yes, damn.
I shot you, all right?
But you wouldn't be seeing
nothing at all
if I hadn't made my move,
so I don't know why
you acting so angry about it.
Oh, you're misinformed.
I'm not angry.
Oh, you're very angry.
No, I'm not angry.
You are angry. It's okay.
I'm not angry.
Except when you keep repeating
"You're angry."
That shit's fucking annoying.
Like a fucking gnat
at a barbecue.
Just...just bugging the fuck
out of me.
Good. I want you to say:
"I'm angry. It's okay.
I'll process my anger.
I love myself. Whoosah."
I don't know what the fuck
you're talking about.
Yes, you do know
what the fuck I'm talking about.
You're the one that
needs therapy.
I did my therapy.
When?
Capt. Howard
made me do it
after I shot all them people
at the airport.
Whoosah.
Whoosah! Officer Mike.
...papi.
Papi. That's "daddy," right?
Yeah.
Whoosah.
Mike, you go
to therapy
to get your issues
worked out...
not bang your therapist.
See, now you just talking nasty.
I gotta survive.
I gotta start loving me for me.
Yeah, that sound like
that group thing talking.
Okay, maybe I did
the group thing once or twice.
♪ Whoosah ♪
And...
Whoosah.
A bunch of men
hugging and kissing.
That's some cult shit.
[♪♪♪]
Right.
Ignore him, doc.
He's blowing this whole thing
out of proportion.
My ass is what's out
of proportion, Mike, okay?
I got a big chunk missing.
It's actually
a small chunk.
You know, man,
this undue tension
you bringing
into this relationship
ain't gonna be healthy
for us in the long run.
Maybe there ain't gonna be
no long run.
Whatever.
He's seeing a shrink.
I mean...
[PHONE RINGS]
Icepick. Lowrey.
Hey, brother.
Two bags? You embarrassed me
in front of my people.
Wait, brother.
No, no, no, brother.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Whatever. You better pray
to whoever it is you pray to,
'cause you got 24 hours
to find that X
before I find you.
The cops hit my mule.
Well, Mr. Tapia, I don't know
where the heat is coming from.
It's a delicate situation
for both of us, isn't it?
I'm telling you,
I've checked them.
Alex, look, look, look.
A guy's OD'ing.
I'm sorry, Mr. Tapia.
I gotta hang up.
Some punk
thinks he can die in my club.
Ecstasy fucks them up.
Get him
out of here, Josef.
Sure, we'll dump him
around the block.
Dump him.
Auntie Syd,
it must be so cool...
Young, single,
living in New York.
Probably hook up with
a lot of cute guys...
just like Sex and the City.
Theresa, cancel
the damn cable.
So, Auntie Syd,
you're a cop too, huh?
Sort of. I mean,
I work for the DEA,
but I just push a lot of papers.
Nothing exciting.
Yeah, well,
you keep pushing papers.
Don't have to worry about
my little sister fighting crime.
Okay?
Possibly getting hurt.
James. Get my screwdriver.
Damn bolts.
Ignore him. He's being mean
because he got injured.
Are you okay?
His wound is fine. It's, um...
other things that were affected.
Oh. Oh!
Theresa!
What?
You...
It's just nerve damage,
that's all.
Y'all not gonna spoil it.
I'll talk to you about it.
[HONK HONK]
It's a donut.
It's a medical thing.
I got it from a maternity store.
You know, pregnant women use it.
They can put one cheek here,
and, like, it take the pressure
off the other cheek.
For you, dawg.
Thoughtful.
Look, man...
uh, you know, last night...
there was something
different in your eyes.
You know, Mike, I had
an epiphany. You know?
I realized you're an enigma.
Yeah, I could see that.
God sent you here to test me.
But guess what?
You not gonna break me,
Mike. No. Whoosah.
Is that Syd?
That's Syd.
Now's not a good time.
Mike, listen,
now's not a good time.
Hit me, hit me,
hit me.
[GLASS SHATTERS]
No throwing balls
in the house!
Whoosah.
What's up, Theresa?
Hey.
Aw, they ain't tell me
it was a luau.
Hey, hey, whoa!
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, Syd,
hold up. Hold up. Hold on.
Behave yourself, girl.
Hey, hold up. Hold up. Hold up.
Oh, look at you. Look at you.
Oh, okay. Okay.
I see now.
You didn't tell Marcus
about New York.
Uh, he knows
About us?
You told him about us?
No, he knows about New York.
You know, it's a nice city,
and that I dropped
a witness off last month.
Mm-hmm.
Mike is so sweet.
So sweet he make
your teeth rot.
So have you
told him yet?
Baby, soon, okay? Real soon.
Well, he needs to know
you're transferring out
and you're not going to be
his partner anymore.
Theresa, timing is everything.
Marcus is not very happy
with me right now.
Mike...
No, no, Syd,
I'm telling you,
that is Scarface
limping around in there.
Really. We need to give
that boy a few minutes
to let his butt
heal up good.
We like each other.
What's the big deal?
I'm just gonna go
tell him right now,
because this is dumb.
Whoa...
Hold up. Hold up. Let me...
I'm gonna tell him.
You know, it ain't like
I ain't gonna tell him.
How am I not tell him?
When?
Okay, I need a minute.
All right?
Straight up. Me and...
We're not vibing right now.
I just need a minute.
Mike, he's my
brother, okay?
Don't be scared.
Toughen up, chief.
Whoa. Hey. Hey,
I ain't saying I was scared.
Just...There's something wrong
with your brother.
So, Mike, I understand
you were in New York last month.
Yeah, I was...um...I did...
Remember? Remember,
I did the thing?
You remember?
Oh, um...
The two of you
should've gotten together.
That would've been
really nice.
Yeah.
Syd, I never told you
Mike was in New York.
Well, you know what,
Mike?
Syd, she's gonna be in town,
what, another week?
Why don't you show her
around Miami?
That'd be nice.
That would be so great.
Yeah. Yeah, I could...
Well, me and...Marcus.
You want to...
You want to show her some stuff?
Yeah, because I'm in
town on vacation.
I'm staying
at the most amazing hotel.
The view, the pool...
Oh, my God.
We got a pool right here.
That ain't exactly a pool, man.
That's like a big-ass puddle
wrapped in blue plastic.
Daddy, didn't they have
any good pools
when you bought
this one?
Megan, that pool cost $3,900.
Okay, so how much
do the good pools cost?
It's all right, baby.
It is kind of whack,
huh?
I gotta go meet somebody.
It was nice seeing you again,
Mike.
Nice...Good to see you.
Where you going?
Bye, sweetie.
I thought you were
on vacation.
So glad you could join us, Mike.
I'm telling you,
spending time like this
make a partnership strong.
Mike, can I see you
by my stupid pool?
What's the deal, baby?
Why you gotta always
come over here
and try to take over,
Mike? Huh?
What are you
talking about?
This is my family,
man. Okay?
What are you
talking about?
My place of peace.
Are you taking
medication?
You taking medicine
for the thing, right?
What'd I do?
Forget it.
Just forget it.
What'd I do?
Mason. Go fetch.
Now, that shit is funny.
That's some funny shit.
[PHONE RINGING]
Oh, man, hold on.
Yo, it's Lowrey, you hot.
$3,900.
3,900.
You better pray to God
you right this time.
Yo, dry off, sweetheart.
That's Icepick.
He said the Haitian Zoepounds
about to do a rip.
Let's move.
All right, guys, smarten up.
Talk to me.
Eyes on, agents. Good luck.
This is 105.
They're backing in.
I got a good look.
We got a good eyeball.
All right, we're in.
What's up?
You come highly recommended
out of New York.
You did some good jobs
for our Russian crew up there.
How old are you?
Old enough.
Come on. If you're going
to move this stuff,
you gotta do it quick.
Wow, nice getup.
You can start
to run these through.
I'd like to see
how your machine works.
Ooh, that sounded dirty.
"I would like to see how
your machine works, baby."
I wouldn't be so crude.
I mean, I'm more of a refined
kind of a human being.
You follow ballet?
Three of my cousins
are dancing
with the famous
Bolshoi Theatre
in Moscow.
I like hippie-hop too.
I gave you 5,000.
SYD:
You gave me 4,900.
I gave you 5,000.
4,900.
5,000.
Count it.
If you want
to fuck with me again,
you can find yourself
another chump.
Okay.
How much?
Three.
Look at this. Money everywhere.
Clean it up.
Okay, we want to change
a little over $3 million,
all right?
How many jobs did you do
with my friends
up there in New York?
Quite a few.
How you behave with me
has consequences
for a lot of people.
You found me,
not the other way around.
You need me to change
small bills to large ones
and make a delivery
to a third party,
and I'd imagine
he'd like his money
in a timely fashion.
Delivery's late, it's your ass,
not mine.
Ooh!
Here's 50,000 in 100s
for your 50,000 in 10s.
Third party
takes his million
in these five
briefcases here.
I hope I'm not
losing you, chief.
I hate math.
So for your $3 million
that we shrunk for you,
you get 2 million
in clean money back,
less our percentage,
$300,000.
I'll be delivering these
to your dealer.
Alexei.
What?
We're giving too
fucking much away.
[SPEAKING IN RUSSIAN]
Yeah, we'll call the
general, renegotiate.
He's a businessman,
we're businessmen.
Yeah, call him.
You call.
Agents, we're on the move
to the money drop.
Forward.
Hey, man, the truck's leaving.
We're going to follow it.
Don't lose that truck.
Follow that truck.
[WHISTLES]
[BLOWS HORN]
Yep, they saddling up.
Look like Icepick came through.
Wonder whose shit
they about to rip now.
[♪♪♪]
Falcon One, do you see her
coming around the corner?
Stand by.
I don't want to get spotted,
take a burn.
Zoepound a bunch of pirates,
man. Steal anything.
Black Suburban at 10 o'clock.
Oh, come on, baby.
Park it at the top.
Roberto, she's coming to you.
I got her.
This is Falcon One, guys.
I got her coming up.
Heads up, guys.
I got an orange muscle car.
Looks to be three
black male occupants.
It's out of our field of vision.
Bring it up.
All right, be aware,
we got three bogeys
unidentified.
Guys, we got three bogeys.
They're splitting up.
They're moving.
Be aware. They're approaching...
Shit. Shit.
Jesus!
Fuck, it's a hit!
Shit.
Agent down. Agent down.
Roberto,
fucking follow them!
I'm on it! I'm on it!
Shit!
Stay here!
Son of a bitch!
It's Syd!
Move! Move!
Man, what is your sister into?
Sidewalk! Sidewalk!
Move! Move! Move!
Shit.
Shit!
I need backup on Canal,
now!
You just get ready to shoot.
Police!
Stop the car!
Man, your badge?
He has a gun! Shoot him!
Mike, she's in
trouble, man.
Move! Get out of the way!
I think I done just got mad.
Gun! Gun! Gun!
Hold on.
Now show them your badge!
This shit is crazy.
I know, right?
Move! Move!
Get the world down here!
Mag!
Go! Go!
Get out!
You, drive!
Go!
Go, go, go, Mike!
Punch that shit! Punch it!
Shit!
Move! Move!
Don't lose her, Mike!
This is what I do!
Aw, shit! Shit.
And definitely shoot
that motherfucker that just...
Oh, man, my headlight.
Shoot back! Shoot back!
Shoot! Shoot!
Oh, man, what the...?!
What are you doing, man?
That's my bad.
Shoot outside!
Pay attention to
what you're doing.
Oh, these dudes
is off the chain!
Jesus! Fuck!
This is some sick shit!
Yep, it's about to
get sicker.
Watch out! Watch out!
Oh, sh...!
Oh, they are not
about to do that.
Hell, yes, they are!
You see that?
They throwing cars!
How am I not see that?
Mike, I'm just trying to help,
okay?
You know what'd be real
fucking helpful, Marcus?
Just shut the fuck up
and let me drive!
Let's try that!
Hey, come on, man,
with the screaming shit!
I'm trying to concentrate
on dodging these motherfuckers.
Just relax.
That motherfucker flipped!
That one
puckered up my butthole.
Almost fucking crushed my head.
The boat!
Whoo!
I lost them.
Yeah, I've got your cargo
to the backup drop point.
[SIRENS APPROACHING]
Attention all units,
suspects still at large.
There she is.
What the fuck
is going on, Syd?
Some desk
you're driving.
Get over here. I'm undercover.
And please call off your dogs.
I got DEA watching my back,
so don't blow my case.
We saved your life.
Yeah, and I appreciate that,
but what I don't appreciate is
you two following me over here,
nearly burning a case
that took five months to set up.
So now we lie
to each other?
Is that what we do?
What do you want me
to do, Marcus?
All right, y'all.
Fuck that, Mike, she's wrong.
Calm down. Relax.
Syd, are there drugs
in that truck?
There's cash.
Where's it going?
I can't tell you that.
Why not?
Because I have a career,
and if I want to keep it,
I have rules to follow.
What's that
supposed to mean?
It means that my orders are
under no circumstances
share information with Miami PD,
because they got
too many leaks.
Oh. I'm Miami PD now?
You done forgot I'm
your big brother, huh?
You know what, Syd?
That shit you did
was reckless,
it was stupid, and it
was dangerous. Okay?
I'm telling Mommy. Okay?
I'm definitely
leaking that shit.
Hey, Marcus...
Syd, come on,
he got a point.
Your brother loves you.
And not to mention
a little thing
called
professional courtesy.
You bouncing around
in somebody's backyard,
you should maybe let them
know about it.
First time
using your gun?
Hey, you handled
yourself very well.
Too bad your partner
didn't notice.
Thanks.
What, you think
you get off that easy?
You been working on this
for five months?
You ain't tell me
while I was in New York?
And what would you
have said?
What? I would've...
You know, I'd have
let you know
this job is rugged,
you know?
And it's dangerous,
and if something happen
to you, I might...
Exactly why I didn't
say anything.
Somebody's
stealing your money.
The drop's done. I gotta go.
Thanks.
We gotta close this case
before it get her killed.
Yeah, no doubt.
Hey, you ready to go
back to the station,
get our asses whupped?
I think we gonna
be all right.
Fellas.
What's your job description?
No, you two.
What is your job description?
I'll tell you. TNT.
Tactical Narcotics Team.
Keyword: "tactical."
"Displaying finesse and subtlety
in achieving a goal."
Tell me, gentlemen...
what was subtle
about your work today?
22 cars...and a boat?
Totaled?
How did you sink a boat?
We didn't sink it.
Hoo. Ha.
Whoosah. Whoosah.
All right, the positive.
Thank God no cops died.
The negative:
I got a police commissioner
so far up my ass,
if he spits,
it's coming out of my mouth,
but I know that there's
always two sides to a story,
so, what's yours?
Well, I was at
a family barbecue.
We got a tip that
the Zoepounders
were gonna do a hit
on cash or drugs
from this big-time X-Man.
That's what they call
a ecstasy dealer
on the streets.
Marcus, I...I know
what they call them.
That's why I'm captain.
It's cool.
So you got the drugs.
No drugs. Oh, okay. All right.
How about the money?
No money.
Well, then, who is this X-Man?
Captain,
I was at a family barbecue,
so I...
We don't know,
but we are going to find out.
Well, then all that...
was for nothing?
Oh, we didn't do all of that.
If you look close...
Watch. Hold up. Let me s...
There's DEA all over.
Wait, the...Wait, hold up.
The DEA? Without consulting me?
That's a DEA car right there.
Christ! Fuck!
Cap. No. Remember
your pressure points.
Do my...My exercises.
[PHONE RINGS]
Holler at your boy.
Whoosah. Whoosah.
Whoosah.
21,000?
What?
Oh, kiss my black ass.
It was the dashboard.
Ooh.
You know what?
Better.
Yeah, you'll get your money.
Yeah, somebody's on they way
with your money.
Captain,
is it possible
we could discuss
potential reimbursement...
Property's not covered,
personal property.
That's why we drive police cars.
So, where do we go from here?
The Zoepounders knew exactly
when to hit the drop,
where to hit the drop,
so we figure they know
where the cash has gone.
We find the cash,
we find the X-Man.
Hey, I'm through playing games,
all right?
I have three cops critical.
I got kids dying
on my streets
from souped-up X.
I do not want these animals
taking over my city.
Do you understand?
So I want you guys
to do whatever you do,
whatever it takes,
but do it now.
[♪♪♪]
It's not good, boss.
Oh, my God.
Fucking ratones eating
my fucking money.
Carlos, this is a stupid
fucking problem to have,
but it is a problem nonetheless.
Rat fuckers.
Boss, it ended up crazy.
This black chica
working for the Russians
was a goddamn maniac lunatic.
She saved your money.
She wasted some Haitians
and got the load
to the backup drop.
Also, Roberto saw these two
crazy gangbanger homeys.
Oh, shit.
Chasing and shooting.
Old days, did I have
this problem? No.
Just fly the drugs in
and ship the money out.
Now American security's
so goddamned tight
over the water
and in the goddamn sky,
that the rats eat my money
before I can get it to Cuba.
You see?
NEWS:
Fiery crash...
I can't even
get my money across town
without making the news.
Hey, man. Man.
Tell me...um...
should I be worried?
No, boss.
Shut the fuck up.
People is trying
to jack my loads
here in Miami.
I own this fucking town.
You see?
This is my town.
Papi, papi!
Oh, my God. Pink.
Pink, niña, pink. Pink.
No powder blue.
Pink is prettier.
But the lady at the store
said I look like a model.
[SMIRK]
You're lucky your mother
was my mother's cousins.
Don't pay attention
to Roberto...
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Besides, models
are filthy creatures.
You look
more like an angel.
What do you think,
Carlos?
Yes, of course.
Roberto,
what do you think?
It's fucking beautiful.
Hey, talk polite
in front of
my little bonbon...
or I'm gonna
chop your balls off.
Hey, dude, for real,
I'm straight with
all your spiritual
enlightenment and shit,
but I need to know
if a crackhead roll up
behind me with a .9,
you're gonna cook that fool.
No question about it.
Shoot him in the leg.
Come on with that leg shit.
Everybody deserves
a little dignity.
What about my dignity?
Your crackhead gonna
be missing a kneecap.
I'm gonna be in a body bag.
So sad.
What's so sad?
Your untreated control issues.
It's not your fault.
What in the hell
is that supposed to mean?
Your mama probably refused you
her tit when you were a baby.
You grew up a malnourished
high-school softie.
Got your gun,
little tight T-shirt,
and became
a overcompensating tough guy.
That is the last time
you will ever
refer to my mother's titties.
I don't even want them
up in your head.
You know, I said all that, Mike,
and all you heard was "titties."
Man, you can't keep suppressing
my spiritual growth, Mike.
You need to suppress
my mother's titties
out of
your psychoanalysis.
You just remember
one thing, my friend.
I may not always
be here.
What's up, Icepick?
Jesus is the way,
my brothers.
Step inside.
You just went number one
on Uncle Mike's shit list.
We got
two lousy bags, man.
My brothers.
Haitian blond with dreads.
Where is he?
Blondie Dread? Uh-uh.
He's very expensive.
You and you have to
do something for me.
Oh, you trying to get gangsta
on me like that?
Yeah, he went gangsta.
So we should probably...
So we want to do the...
Yeah, sure.
Me and my partner, we're on
the Miami PD tandem dance team.
We got a routine.
We won all the local
talent shows.
We thinking about
going national.
You want to show him
some of the routine?
Ooh, warm it up.
Don't hurt nothing.
Yo, yo, watch this. Watch this.
This the shit right here.
This is the shit.
♪ It's your birthday
It's your birthday ♪
♪ It's your birthday ♪
What you doing
to my shop, man?
Watch this spin.
Wait.
What are you doing?
Oh, give me some.
You're ruining my shop. Stop!
Do the dance thing.
I'm gonna bring the house down.
No! No!
Stop!
He lives in a pink house
eight blocks from here
on Carl Street.
Police! Get down.
Police!
Who that? Who in my house?
I'm the devil. Who's asking?
The devil is not welcome here!
You got to call yourself
the devil in his house? Shit!
You're in my house!
This is all your fault!
You're in my country, though.
Fuck you, how's that?
I'm gonna kill you,
motherfucker!
Your country, my ass!
Fuck you.
Fuck me? Fuck you!
You no problem!
Mike, do you have to be
so combative?
Fucking...!
You calling me a bitch? Hey?
Yo...
Do or die, man!
A bullet in the head'll
really mess up your extensions.
Take your bullet
and eat that shit, man.
How about that?
[GUNFIRE]
What the fuck?
Sir, we just want to talk.
You want to talk?
Well, go ahead. Go ahead.
We're not Immigration.
They can't hear you because
they're still shooting at you.
Fucking Haitians
in a fucking little-ass room
with fucking guns. Shit!
Got to make it home
to my babies.
Damn, now.
Motherfucker!
You killed my brother!
That's a bitch!
Shoot them. Fucking shoot them.
They shot me.
They got me, man. Yo!
Got you.
Oh, shit! Motherfucker!
They killed the boy!
They kill me!
They're killing everybody!
Motherfucker!
I'm gonna kill you,
motherfucker!
Come. Come kill me,
motherfucker.
Come on.
You don't take me alive.
You have three seconds
to drop your weapon!
I got a present for you!
A nice present for you!
One!
Two!
I'm gonna kill you.
Don't shoot.
Don't shoot, man.
Don't kill me.
You know, the...
Bullets, man, all...
Excuse me.
You all right, man?
Apologize to that man.
Apologize! Apologize.
Hey, listen, I owe you...
It's just that, you know,
you was disrespect...
But that don't mean
it give me the right,
though. It don't.
Excuse me. Whoosah. Whoosah.
Whoosah, motherfucker!
[KICK]
See, the interesting
thing is
he's the one of us
that's not pissed off.
I don't know nothing.
Whoa, I didn't ask you
no question yet!
I don't know
nothing.
Lying to me already?
How'd you know about the drop?
I don't know
nothing!
Stop lying!
Do you know anything?
I'm gonna be nice about it.
Let's ask
some other suspects.
Hey, look, man, fuck it.
No, let's try this.
Let's talk to his homeys.
Hey, look here, man.
Can you tell me who was driving
the black Suburban? Huh?
Oh, he don't know nothing.
His brains
is under the end table.
Oh. Sh...
He can't tell us shit, Mike.
He's all fucked up.
What's your point?
Dead suspects can't say shit.
Well, it seems like
live suspects
don't say shit either,
so I'm gonna go ahead
and hot this dude here.
Save us the paperwork.
I don't know nothing!
I don't do motherfucking
surveillance, man.
He do surveillance,
man.
He don't let nobody
touch his camera.
What's on that camera?
Trigger Mike strikes again.
Hi, welcome to Phat's.
How can I help you?
Miami PD.
Whoa. Cops.
I love that show.
We need to see what's
on this videotape.
Absolutely.
You got a little
bullet hole in there.
You guys tell me about it?
Guess not. Okay. All right.
Okay, we'll put this
in our central floor model.
It's got kick-ass bass.
You guys like hip-hop music?
I love hip-hop.
Sometimes we freestyle
in the break room.
If you guys ever want
to kick it, we'll flow.
All right, we're gonna
set you up on the wide-screen.
Correct ratio...
Spanish Palms Mortuary.
Why would they
be doing surveillance
at a funeral home?
Is that a Cuban flag?
Uh, uh...right there.
See the gun?
Never knew
the guards at funeral homes
needed to carry
them kind of weapons.
It just seems like
we should turn it off,
you know,
because my dad owns the store.
She got a tongue ring.
This is like a porno.
We're not...
Dude. Dude.
All right?
Yeah.
Okay. Okay.
It's just, you know,
my dad's gonna be...
I just need to...I think I...
[MOANING]
This is official
police business.
What the fuck's
going on here?
Out of my way.
My dad is coming.
What the hell is going on
in my store?
Son, how did this porno crap
get on my videos in my store?
What the hell is
going on in here?
You all right?
No, I'm not
all right, Mike.
Three days
of this shit.
Got my nerves
all rattled.
My ass still hurts...
from what you did to it
the other night.
Oh, my Lord.
Yeah, it got rough.
You know?
I mean, we got caught up
in the moment, shit got crazy.
You know how I get.
When you popped me from behind,
I think
you damaged some nerves.
Okay.
Now I can't...
Can't what?
I can't even get an erection.
What's an erection?
I tried taking Viagra, you know,
pop one, pop two.
Been eating them like Skittles.
That poor man is
pouring out his heart.
And I'm still flaccid.
Um, okay.
I'm comfortable
talking to you...
It's got 5.1 Dolby.
MIKE: ...about what I did
to your ass...
but you not getting
an erection...
that's a real problem
for me.
I just figured
I could talk to you.
Yeah, yeah, no, no.
We're partners,
but we are partners
with boundaries.
We got a new rule.
From now on, you can't say
the word "flaccid" to me.
He's a mean fuck.
Look here.
This is our little boundary box.
So we gonna take
the word "flaccid,"
and we're gonna put it in there
with my mom's titties...
with your erection problems,
and we're gonna
close this box...
and we're gonna throw this bitch
in the ocean,
and the only way that you can
get to this box
is you got to be motherfucking
Jacques Cousteau.
We cool?
Naw.
Oh, shit.
We gotta go.
In front of my babies
you got porno
and homo shows up in here?
What kind of freak-ass store
is this?
And you two motherfuckers
need Jesus.
Cover your ears, baby.
Palm Mortuary, owned by
an offshore holding company,
which, after 17 layers
of bullshit,
turns out to be registered
to Donna Maria Tapia,
mother
of Hector Juan Carlos Tapia,
who calls himself
"Johnny."
Johnny Tapia. Shit.
Looks like every time
the PD goes after him,
he sues for wrongful arrest.
And, oh, does he win.
Look. Last year
he was awarded $9 million,
and got a dozen
dumb-ass officers like you
fired.
Well, he hasn't
run across us yet.
You know, we'd sure like to hear
what's going on in that house.
Yeah, use your computer brain
and tap the phone.
Well, um, well...
that happens
to be highly illegal
without a judge.
Um, we were thinking
of something
more along the lines
of a training operation.
No, no, no, I can't do that.
Get you tickets
to the Heat game.
I need floor seats.
With them thick-ass glasses,
you don't need floor seats.
The man can see the game
from the parking lot.
See, I can't work
under these conditions.
Floor seats to the Heat.
You got it.
Lakers.
Yes, Lakers.
Okay. Watch me work.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Hello? Is this
the pest control?
Yeah. We got a fucking problem.
You know where we live.
Yeah, South Miami.
We got it.
Got our way in.
Illegally?
You got to put a word to it.
It's like, secret.
So, y'all want to kill roaches?
Illegal.
Look, we go
in, plant a couple gypsy wires,
find out what Tapia's up to.
These are your basic
household bugs.
Dawg, this is what we do.
What's the sprayers for?
The roaches.
Roaches? We got rats.
Say what?
Uh, that's not going
to be an issue.
We can handle that.
We're just going to
have to adjust
our approach
a little bit.
Nope. Nope.
I don't mess with no rats.
Hey. Stop it.
We're in. Get your head right.
Mike, I'm a grown-ass man.
Well, get your grown-ass
self together,
and let's do this.
This is a beautiful
house you got here, sir.
Well, start looking.
They're all over.
Oh!
Oh, uh, those ain't
normal rats.
What he means is that...
that they're obviously
a special breed.
Well, what kind of breed
are they?
Big motherfuckers.
Taking care
of these rats
is not going
to be a problem,
but are going
to need to make sure
they're not breeding
in other sections of the house.
Yeah, at Zook...
we like to, uh, work
from the outside in,
you know?
So we're going
to leave these...
Excuse me.
Um, we're going to
leave these here
and send in a special unit.
It probably would
be better
if we began in
the rest of the house.
You're not getting
near the rest of the house.
Sir, we're not going to be able
to guarantee our work.
Listen,
the only thing
that we can guarantee
is that these rats are
going to keep fucking,
you know, giving
off offspring,
until we find
the colony.
Rats don't got
no stinking colony.
Well, actually,
these are colonial rats.
What they do is
they send out worker rats
that are called...
Marsupials.
These drones,
they're explorers
of the rat world,
you know?
They just looking
for rat pussy.
[LAUGHING]
Are you fucking with me?
Hold on. You called us.
We can leave,
but what you should understand
is that these rats
are going to hump twice a day.
All right. Down there.
Just kill them
and bring me the bill.
That's that bullshit.
That's that bullshit
right there.
You see these rats?
Plant your wires.
You're not
leaving me here...
Plant your wires.
Gentlemen. Alexei, Josef.
Oh, I really like
that word, Johnny.
"Gentlemen."
I'm just trying
being civil.
This is business,
we can all relax.
Alexei, would you like
a good Cohiba?
Why not?
Of course,
and you, Josef?
I'm told you are quite
a wine connoisseur.
I am.
Carlos, have Josef
pick a good wine
from the cellar,
and Alexei and I
will have a cigar.
Come on.
[SPEAKS SPANISH]
Where the fuck
you going?
Uh, pretty bad problem
you got up here.
I'm going to head
down to the truck,
get some poison
pellets and stuff.
Come straight back.
No screwing around.
[CRASHING FURNITURE]
They're all over.
Nice place
you got here.
It's Mama's,
and it's a shithole.
Built a fucking
million years ago.
Expensive shithole, eh?
Oh, no.
My new place,
the one I'm building in Cuba.
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
Almost finished.
Everything fucking shiny new.
Come on upstairs.
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
Oh, shit.
Oh, shit!
Look at the balls
on that motherfucker.
Roberto...
the camera's out
in the general's office.
Everything in this house
is broken.
My wire's planted.
How about yours?
Almost got three wires planted.
Mike!
There's a papa rat
humping the shit
out of this mama rat.
No, he's straight
pile-driving her.
Now, how is that information
going to help me do my job?
They fuck just like us.
Where's the pest guy?
There's something going on
down here.
Goddamn rats.
Yeah, they everywhere,
just like cockroaches.
No disrespect,
but I do not wish
to talk business
until my partner return.
It's baffling.
You decide you want
to pay me less money,
and you talk about respect?
Let's wait for Josef.
You know, me and digits...
Carlos...
could you please bring Josef in?
[SPEAKS IN SPANISH]
So...
your partner is here.
Would you like to talk now?
Carlos, another box.
So you sign over
ownership papers
for all the Florida
clubs you own,
and I will control everything
from point of origin
to sale, okay?
No middleman.
Especially Russian middleman.
With all due respect,
Mr. Tapia,
in my country,
I see such things all the time.
I'm sorry for your country.
That's got to be
some Cuban stupid tradition
to put them
in a tortilla bin.
Now, listen to me,
you Russian punk.
I, me, Johnny Tapia,
will sever your head off!
You kill me,
and you will have a shit-storm.
Should I screw
your young wife...
or visit your son,
the soccer player?
My daughter knows your son.
You're going to regret this.
I hope that we can
remain friends,
because at the end,
what else do we have
but friendship, trust,
honor?
Without this,
we are no more than beasts.
The kitchen monitor's out.
What the hell's going on
out there?
Shit.
I found something.
It's a guy's finger.
What? What, did the rats
eat the rest of him?
What the fuck
are you doing?
Oh, hey,
I was just looking for you.
I think I figured out
what your problem is.
Y'all a bunch of filthy
motherfuckers.
Jose...
Blow out!
What's going on? Shit.
Get out of the house!
Blow out, blow out!
This shit's got to stop.
Fuck!
We should go.
Hold it!
Go! Go!
Just another day
with Mike Lowrey.
Damn! Go!
Come on!
Roberto thinks they
were the gangbangers
that tried to hijack
the drop, boss.
How did this thing happen?
I don't know.
We called
the rat people,
and these guys
showed up.
Maybe you're
the rat, huh?
They tried
to steal from me,
and you let them
into my mother's house.
Johnny. Hey, no.
I would never...
Nobody puts in danger
my daughter, my mother...
or my money.
Send him to
the mortuary.
Johnny! Johnny,
what happened to Roberto?
He killed himself, Mama.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Very sad.
Make sure and write
a nice letter to his mother.
I'll do it.
Okay. Bye.
Yo, run the print.
Hey, Mike, stop playing, man.
Run the print.
Don't touch me with no fucking
dead finger. I'm serious.
Excuse me, run this print.
I need to find the owner.
Thank you.
Fletcher, think you can
find out
what's on these shreds?
Of course.
Señoritas.
Listen, we're thinking
about ordering
a little bit
of lunch.
Should we put you down
for a bucket
of extra-crispy
and a couple of
cream sodas?
"Couple of cream sodas."
That's very funny.
That's hilarious.
Isn't it low tide?
You know, I think it is.
Don't you have some
relatives to pick up?
What?
Yo, now you crossed
the line, man.
Okay, no,
that's not funny.
We're fucking with you.
Look, we planted some wires,
we need some help. No bullshit.
I want you...
to find out...
who those two black
puta de mierda are,
and I want them
lying right here...
in Mama's garden
in these coffins.
And our mystery
finger belongs to...
Josef Kuninskavich.
Oh, man, this dude
was a lieutenant
in a Russian mob.
Owned a couple dozen
Florida nightclubs.
Tapia's starting to knock
off Russian mob bosses.
Got something.
What you got,
dickhead?
The computer
matches half tones,
gray tones,
densities.
Sort of like a visual
code-breaking.
Little something I put together.
The shredded papers
you found was a photograph.
Some kind of boat.
Dixie 7.
It's registered to a one
Floyd Poteet.
The Poteet brothers.
One of the KKK guys
we busted.
You blew his ear off,
remember?
Mike, can you teach me
how to shoot people?
Listen to what we got
at Tapia's.
[IN SPANISH]
Si, boss.
Now, this is
the second-in-command talking.
He's telling him,
"Yes, boss.
"We found a bunch
of fat doe fuckers,
and we're getting
them emptied."
Fat does emptied?
The hell does
that mean?
He has a meeting this afternoon.
[REWINDING TAPE]
TAPIA:
You know who I am?
SYD: Name sounds
familiar.
TAPIA: Sense of humor.
I like that.
Meet me on the sand,
2:00, Shore Club.
She has no idea.
Let's roll.
Y'all come with us.
I ordered us a couple
of Bacardi Mojitos.
Mojito...
Miami...
Okay, zoom in on nine.
A little more audio, please.
So why don't we
take a swim? Cool off.
Or we could just stay here
and get drunk. How about that?
Or we could drink this later.
Unless you have a reason
why you don't want to get that
beautiful body of yours wet.
Why don't you just ask me
if I'm wearing a wire?
I'd rather go swimming.
What the hell's he doing?
Son of a bitch.
Shit, he's taking her
into the water.
This guy's smart.
I want you to
work for me, okay?
Why waste time on this
unnecessary conversation?
It's very unnecessary.
What do you need
with another banker?
For the same reason
as your previous employer.
But now I own all
the Russian clubs.
No middleman.
You know, I'm about to be
the biggest importer
and distributor of ecstasy
in North America.
You're going to be
a very rich young woman.
That's why
I thought...
I know what you thought,
Mr. Tapia.
As long as you don't think it
more than once,
I'm happy to be
in business with you.
All right.
Let's do business.
What are you, a cop or a model?
What you talking
about, man?
I threw something on.
I like looking good. What?
For who?
Hey, don't hate the player.
Hate the game.
I hate the tailor.
Good job.
We'll get him.
Your brother would
love to talk to you
down the street.
Whoa, what's
going on?
You guys trying
to blow my case
or just insane?
You're the one
taking a little dip
with the Cubano maniac.
How'd you know that?
We had a wire
in the house.
You two have a warrant
for that wire?
Look, fuck that, okay?
You don't know
the kind of danger
that you're in, Syd.
I am fully aware,
and I am fully capable
of what I am doing.
Marcus, I am not
your baby sister anymore.
For the DEA,
you ain't nothing
but a honeypot.
What'd you just say?
Look, that's why
you got the job,
because you look good
in a bathing suit.
All right, let's
sit down somewhere.
All right, look, Syd,
there's some shit
you need to know.
Johnny Tapia is cutting up
Russian mob bosses
in his mom's kitchen.
In the kitchen, Syd.
He found a severed finger
by the crock pot.
You're about to be in the middle
of a drug war.
No disrespect, but Miami PD
has arrested this guy 12 times
with no convictions.
Why don't you guys
just hang back
and let us
bring him down?
Guys, look, I need this, okay,
and I am this close.
What's "this close"?
I'm in charge
of money laundering
for his entire operation.
In a month or two we'll have
enough for a conviction,
and this whole thing
will be over with.
What about a day or two?
Sound better?
Marcus and I
think we found the key
to Tapia's
whole operation.
You have nothing to say
now, huh? Just stuck, right?
Okay...
time out, y'all. Damn!
We got this peckerwood
that's going to put us down
with the transport end
of Tapia's operation.
Do you want in?
Mike, why would you...
When?
Tonight.
Page me.
Should I bring my thong?
Get your bitch hands off!
I'll knock you the fuck out!
Mike, we're trying to keep
her out of trouble, man,
not invite her in.
Man, I just
figured, you know,
if she with us,
that's just less trouble
she could get into.
I'm going to keep it
real with you too, man.
I think she can
handle herself.
I'm going to keep it
real with you.
Don't nobody
know my sister
the way I do, okay?
She doesn't
make good choices, Mike.
She's not
street-smart.
Doesn't make good...
Like, what kind
of choices?
Men, for one.
She's attracted
to these dumb,
flashy, just musclebound
dickheads, Mike, you know?
Cock diesel motherfuckers
that can't even fucking turn
to wipe
their ass, Mike.
You feel me?
Yeah.
You know?
Just dumb as a bucket of shrimp.
Yeah. Yeah, that shit's crazy.
I mean, you don't think
maybe you...
maybe you
didn't, like,
get a chance to know
any of them?
I'm going to give
the next one a chance.
A chance
to whup his ass.
Whup the shit
out of him.
Oh, you going to fight him?
What I'm going to do
ain't even going
to be legal.
I might be up in here
with these motherfuckers.
Do you know what I mean?
The fuck you looking at?
Thank you kindly.
Who sprung me?
Hey, Cousin Floyd.
Oh, you.
Remember me?
Cheese.
Y'all look great together.
What the fuck
you doing?
Oh, no, just
a little insurance.
You going to help us find
Dixie 7,
and let us know what that boat
has to do with Johnny Tapia.
I ain't no snitch.
Oh, you ain't no snitch?
Oh, damn. That's a shame.
Know what I'm going to do?
I'm going to send
a special 8 x 10
to his KKK buddies back in jail.
You know what?
It's a digital photo too.
So we can pretty much
do whatever we want
to do with it.
Hey, look, by the time
we get done with you,
you going be in the next
Busta Rhymes video on BET.
Tuck ass.
I got my rights.
I'm worried.
There's too much heat
around in Miami.
I can feel it.
We need to put my money
in coffins to Cuba faster.
You should tell the mortuary
to speed things up. All right?
That's the channel marker
way out there.
They make the drop
mostly at dawn,
but there'll be one today,
though.
Syd, you talk to Mama?
She's got hives.
Oh, and I told Mama
about your Cubano boyfriend.
He ain't invited
to Christmas dinner.
Change the station.
More music, less Marcus.
If you open the door,
he'll be a black Dr. Phil
for the next 40 minutes.
Syd, you might not want
to get too flirty with Mike.
Your boyfriend might cut off
his trigger finger.
Maybe Mike's been
flirting with me.
Did you ever think
about that?
Ooh...Mm-mm.
Trigger Mike?
Not like this.
Don't play with the boy.
Seriously.
Just tell him about New York.
Do it.
Tell me what?
Oh, shit. Is he
walking down the steps?
Oh, shit.
He coming down.
It's okay.
Yeah, you done
fucked up.
You done fucked up.
Um, you remember...
Remember I went to New York?
You remember?
And...I said, "Syd."
I ran in...
Syd ran into me
in New York
on the street in that place.
And I said, "What's up?"
And we was hungry,
so then...
she had fish.
It was grouper,
and then I had
some chicken.
Remember I was supposed
to come home,
but I didn't?
We went out on a date.
Five, actually.
Now we're seeing
each other.
Hold up.
You know, really out of
respect for you, Marcus,
you know,
nothing happened.
Hey, Mike,
why you tripping, man?
I mean, we wanted to make sure
that you was cool with it.
Doesn't matter
what I think, you know?
Hey, I had to find out
like this, right?
Don't matter.
Let me ask you,
y'all going
to have babies?
Little bunch of mini Mikes?
Bunch of little lying,
violent motherfuckers?
Marcus, nothing happened.
I just want to say,
Mama's going to be thrilled.
All right,
you know what?
You need to go ahead and
"whoosah" or something
for a second.
Hey, hey,
here comes the Dixie 7.
Whoosah.
Mike, just leave it alone.
Why you acting
like that?
Hey, Mike, go on about
your business, man.
No, we're going
to talk about this.
No, get out of my face.
I'm trying to talk to you.
Get the fuck off me, Mike.
What the hell is
your problem, man?
Why you acting so stupid?
This is a dysfunctional
partnership.
That's why the fuck
I'm acting like that.
There ain't no trust,
Mike.
I didn't lie to you!
I was waiting for the
right time to tell you,
but that ain't
what your issue is.
Why don't you
bring it to me real?
What is your problem
with this?
You know what?
You a dog, man.
That's it. There it is.
I said it.
Oh, okay.
You like a pit bull
with that little pink thing
hanging out, Mike.
Oh, it's like that.
Oh, okay.
I'm not good enough
for your sister.
Guys, enough. The boat's coming.
Okay. We going to
handle that shit.
Go ahead, man.
In about an hour,
the drop boat's going to come.
We got them.
Wonder what mortuary
that coffin's going to.
Keep going straight by.
You seeing what I'm seeing?
Get the load to the mortuary,
and don't screw up.
I got it.
Load up.
They're getting away!
Stop! Stop!
We need your car.
All right?
Get out of the car.
Can you not get a better car
than that?
Let that man go!
Don't be coming at me
with that tone, Mike.
Freak.
Small cars don't fuck up
the ozone layer.
That's what
I'm talking about.
Stop the car.
Get...Yeah.
Pop the trunk.
Get out. Get in.
Get out. Get out.
Get your ass in.
Okay.
I am in the middle of a sale.
Do I have to pull my gun?
Oh, shit. Dan Marino.
What's up?
Back up, Dan.
Hey, you're the truth.
Whatever you need,
officers.
That's Dan Marino.
Hey. Back up.
Let me know how it rides.
Oh, he's gonna
test-drive the shit out this.
Go. I don't want
to blow my cover.
Got them. Got them right there.
Mike, why do you got
to get so close?
I'm not going to let
that coffin get away.
But they're all around us,
man.
Shit, those are the gangbangers.
Relax, they don't
know us.
Boss, we got a problem here.
We're being followed.
This is a big problem, Carlos.
Sorry, boss.
I'll take care of it, okay?
You kill those black bitches.
All right?
Shit. I think they made us.
Get some undercovers
to roll with us.
Okay, we're splitting up.
Everybody go
to Third and Boxter, now!
Here we go.
I didn't sign up
for no goddamned car chase!
Have you lost your mind?
Mike, I see you got your mind
set on doing dumb shit,
so please let me out!
I seen this in a movie once.
They didn't make it!
Mike!
Oh, shit!
Dump truck!
I got it.
Mike!
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Whoa! Whoa! Mike! Whoa!
Right there!
Oh, shit, Mike!
Did you see that shit?
No shit.
Dan Marino should
definitely buy this car.
But not this one.
I'm fucking this one up,
but he should definitely
get one like this.
All right,
that was almost fucked up.
I almost fucked up.
This is not necessary.
Oh, shit!
Dead man on
the hood! Dead man!
I'm trying
to get it off.
I'm trying to
get it off.
That shit's nasty.
That's nasty.
That shit is nasty.
Undercover police!
Everybody move!
Undercover police! Move!
Move! Move! Move!
Oh!
Coming around the corner now!
Get ready, they're coming
around the block. Move!
Shit! Boy, if this was my car,
I'd be pissed!
Get down! Get down!
Trying to break
the world record
for gun fights in a week?
This is not the time
to criticize!
I can't work with you
blaming shit on me
all the time!
This is not your fault?
This is not. No. No!
Bullshit, Mike!
Everything's your fault!
Okay, let's go! Let's go!
Clear around! Cool!
I'm going around!
Mike, got him!
They got the coffin.
Move!
Move! Move! Get down!
Police! Get down!
Move! Move!
Police! Move! Move!
Get out of my way!
Move! Move!
Open the door! Police!
Whoa! Shit!
Mike! Mike!
That boy bit me!
Mike!
Move! Move!
Police! Move!
He under there?
We lost the coffin,
and you barbecued
our only lead, Mike.
This has got to be the worst,
most emotional cop week
of my life.
Yeah, it's been a little rough.
Where were
these bodies going?
I don't know.
It's really strange.
All the John Does
we found out here are empty.
Empty Does. Fat Does.
Cut them open,
took the organs out,
sewed them back up.
Nice work.
The more you guys fuck up,
the more we look
like rock stars, baby.
The van you was chasing
is a transport for
the city morgue.
These John Does here
were being delivered
to the university
for medical research.
Nice going.
I can't believe you guys.
Do you both wake up
in the morning,
call each other up?
"Good morning, Marcus."
"Good morning, Mike."
"How you doing?" "A'ight."
"So, how are we going to fuck up
the captain's life today?"
"Gee, I don't know."
"I don't know."
"Ooh. Look, over there.
Let's kill three fat people
and leave them on the street."
Hey, they were dead
before we ran over them.
It doesn't matter whether they
were dead or not, goddamn it!
Every time you leave a corpse
on the street,
I have to get
these forensic coroner guys
to come
and to see what happened.
Then I've got to get detectives.
See? They're detecting shit.
Then I've got to get
these forensic guys
to stick them back
in the fucking bag!
Jesus Christ!
You guys, you're like...
You're like a bunch
of bloodsucking ticks
draining the life's blood
out of this department.
Whoosah.
Damn the whoosah,
captain.
Did you just
call me a tick?
I was referring to him.
Captain, these are not
normal corpses.
If I threw you
out of a speeding ice truck
and then ran over your head,
you wouldn't be normal either.
Think about this
for one second.
All of these bodies
have been emptied out
from a drug smuggler
that just happens
to own a mortuary,
and I got a bunch
of bodies hanging around
with plenty of room
in them...
I could smuggle some shit.
Johnny Tapia
has the perfect cover.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Johnny Tapia?
Yes. I want a warrant to go
into his mortuaries immediately.
No warrant. What?
For what? For what?
For a bunch of dead guys
on their way
to med research?
No. Every time we go after him,
he sues us and wins.
This shit stops now
or they'll fire us, disband TNT,
and stick me
in a fucking coffin.
This is over now!
What happened to
"whatever it takes"?
That was pre-vehicular
manslaughter.
Not to mention
Johnny Tapia...
[BANGING]
What the fuck is that?
Oh, shit.
Shut up. Shut up.
This man has violated
my rights!
Who the fuck is that?
Running people over
is not enough for you?
Now you're into kidnapping?
Captain, that man
is a criminal. Okay?
We busted him at the...
Excuse me. I have so
much brass up my ass
I could be playing
"The Star-Spangled Banner."
I ain't cut out
for this, man.
Come on, man. I can't do this
with you right now.
I'm re-evaluating
what's important.
About what? Being a cop?
No, about you
being my partner.
Is this about Syd?
God! Hey, Marcus, man...
That was messed up,
but that ain't what
this is about, Mike.
Once we nail Tapia,
you and me, we're over.
I already signed
my transfer papers.
Megan, what's the
name of this boy
taking you to the movies?
Reggie.
Daddy, please don't embarrass me
and ask him a lot of questions.
Everybody knows
you're a cop,
and it makes
people nervous.
Well, why nervous? He on crack?
[DOORBELL RINGS]
It's cool?
Yeah. Come in.
What'd you...?
I got a sneak and peek.
Judge Sinclair said
we can go into
the mortuary tonight.
We can't touch nothing,
but if we find something,
he said he'll give us
a righteous warrant.
You love pissing
Captain Howard off,
don't you?
Hey. It's what I do.
So, when you start
playing golf?
Hey, so you real serious
about this
transfer thing, huh?
I mean, you been quitting
for 10 years.
I just always thought it was,
you know,
how you dealt
with all this shit.
It's what's best
for me and my family.
Look, I'm gonna get
my stuff, man.
Mm.
"We ride together,
we die together.
Bad boys for life."
[DOORBELL RINGS]
We getting old,
Mike.
One of them young punks
coming
to take my baby out
on her first date.
Who the fuck are you?
Hi, Mr. Burnett. I'm Reggie.
What you doing here?
I came to take out Megan.
What?
How old are you?
I'm 15, Mr. Burnett.
Motherfucker,
you look 30.
Show me some ID.
I don't have none on me.
You don't have no ID.
Get your ass up
against that wall.
What the fuck
is your problem?
You think you know it all.
Little young Thundercats.
You got joints on you?
You smoke
that shit?
No, sir.
You trying to get
my daughter high?
Do you smoke that shit?
Marcus! Nigga, who that
at the door?
It's Reggie.
Who the fuck is Reggie?
Came to take Megan out.
What you want, nigga?
I'm here to take
his daughter out.
What's your name?
Reggie.
I heard the motherfucker
say your name Reggie.
You taking Megan out?
How old is you?
Fifteen.
Shit, nigga,
you at least 30.
This is Mike.
Can you fight?
Yeah.
You can fight?
Motherfucker.
You can't fight.
Look at you.
Mike, Mike...
I want to know if...
When somebody
taking my niece out,
I want to know
if he can fight.
Somebody might
come say something,
the nigga can't fight,
she can't go.
This is Megan's
godfather, okay?
He just got out the joint.
Why you putting all my
business in the street?
They call him...
I just got out of jail,
and I ain't going back!
I ain't going back!
What's wrong with you?
You acting all scared.
Nigga, you ain't never
seen a gun before?
Mike, stop pointing
the gun at the boy, man.
Nigga, look, don't
you disrespect me
in front of company.
All right,
let the gun go off.
Nigga, you a big, old,
tall Ludacris-looking
motherfucker, ain't you?
You rap?
No.
♪ Move, nigga, get out the way ♪
♪ If I see you on the highway
Get the fuck outta my way ♪
Hey, Mike!
Now, listen.
Have my daughter
home at 10:01.
If she ain't home
at 10:01,
I'm in the car, okay?
Lock, loaded, and hunting
your motherfucking ass down.
Do you hear me?
Speak up,
Reggie.
I'll go with him.
And if I'm there, know
what it's going to be?
Chitty Chitty
Bang Bang, nigga.
That's what it's going to be.
THERESA: Marcus!
Oh, Reggie, baby,
I am so sorry.
Please forgive Megan's dad
and his silly friend.
You a virgin?
Yes.
Keep it that way. Ain't gonna be
no fucking tonight.
Baby, the red shirt's nice.
I like that.
You guys have a good time.
You ever made love
to a man?
No.
You want to?
No, sir.
Hey, have
a good time, baby.
MEGAN: Go. Go.
All right.
MEGAN: We need to go.
That was cool.
So, you ready to
bust this case open?
Oh, yeah. Let's finish
strong, all right?
[♪♪♪]
All right, ladies.
We cannot take a burn tonight,
or Tapia walks.
I need a good, clean break-in.
Zank, eyeball.
Eyeball set.
Dex, high ground.
Rooftop set.
Fanuti, light your crack pipe.
Gotcha.
Lockman, you buzzing?
We're up, baby.
[BUZZ]
Hello, anybody home?
We got a stiff to deliver!
What's going on here, man?
We got a stiff
to deliver.
Nobody told me about any stiff.
No, the guy's in the van
right now. He's fresh.
There's no deliveries
tonight.
They told us to come
right over to the place.
This is the place.
My friend, we've got to
bring him in here.
No one in.
You guys get that body
to the morgue yet?
Morgue?
You said to get it to
the Spanish Palms Mortuary.
No, you dumb Latin fuck.
What are you smoking
in that crack pipe?
Hey, who you calling
a Latin fuck, man?
Check.
There's burnt people down here,
Mike.
Oh, fuck.
Damn, somebody's teeth.
Now that we're here,
we're going to need you
to sign some paperwork,
because the man
is very contagious,
and his contagiousness
could touch you.
You guys have a nice evening.
Good night.
Might you see us inside
for some hot cocoa?
Cam one, I got a good signal.
Cam two,
I got a good signal.
Oh. Oh...
Hey, hey, hey.
Damn!
Stop it. Do not
do that tonight.
You don't smell that?
Oh, yeah, I smell it.
It stinks.
Stop!
I'm gonna have
some Pepto.
This dude hasn't
been embalmed yet.
What the hell
you talking about?
What they do, they stick
a tube down your throat
and they just suck out
all the gunk and bile,
because what happens is
your body'll get gaseous
and you'll decompose,
and they don't want
that shit to happen
before your family
see you.
Mike, I really don't need
to know that now.
They sew your mouth closed.
They got to get all
of that out,
because a lot of times,
dead people'll fart.
That shit'll clear
a funeral home out.
How do you know
all that?
Oh, Learning Channel.
That shit got me.
Oh, shit.
You're not even gonna
warm up to it?
Hey! Do some cop work.
He's a human being.
Check the casket.
Why don't you check his spine
while you're in there?
I'm retching...
Mike!
What?
Have some dignity.
I ain't doing nothing.
Cover her titties up.
Like, what am I gonna do
with these big-ass dead titties?
But you're looking, though.
There's...Something's wrong
with your brain.
Just cover the titties.
God...
damn!
Damn. This nicer
than some cribs.
She's going to Cuba.
Who's top cop now? Huh?
That's what I'm talking about.
See? There you go.
That's it right there.
Take a picture of the money,
then check this body.
Nah, I'm gonna count these.
You know?
Check the body.
I'm gonna check the body, Mike.
I'm not rushing into it,
that's all.
This one's going to
a mortuary in L.A.
I'm gonna check this one.
That's that bullshit
that I be
talking about.
Mike, the motherfucking head
fell off.
Come here.
I'm...I'm...
I'm back in the...game. Hoo!
Think I got something.
Feels like a bag.
Shit, no, it's his kidney.
I smell dead people.
Drugs and money.
We got him, baby.
This dude is loaded.
Bet he thinks
he's a damn genius,
transporting them
in dead bodies, huh?
Let's get this body.
Mike, you've
got company, man.
Somebody's coming. Hide.
Give me the X.
You gotta stall them.
[ALARM RINGS]
Hide! Hide! Hide!
Shit!
Punk kids do this?
Go check it out.
Hide!
Marcus! Why would you...?
That's just not smart, man.
You tell Theresa,
I'll kill you.
Bimbo's next.
Oh, God. Not that.
Not the bimbo.
Let's hurry this shit up.
Shit.
We got a big problem.
We got a big, big problem.
Drive that ambulance
into the building right now.
Crash that ambulance
into the building!
No, no. Not me, baby.
I got too many crashes
on my file. You do it.
No, no, man.
You're kidding.
I got red-flagged by
administration last month
for the thing, you know?
You know how much the city
had to pay for that.
I can't have another
ding on my file.
Mike, my man, we want to
help you out here, you know,
but we got a couple
of administration problems
over here, you know
what I'm talking about,
so how about we give you
sirens and
some flashing lights?
Make a racket. How's that?
Negative! Negative!
Crash that ambulance
into the building right now!
We want to help the team out
and everything, but...
but I'm not getting
suspended for this.
Okay, I plan on
whupping y'all asses
the second I get out of here.
Crash that ambulance into
the building right now!
Screw it. Just the price
of cop business, my man.
Now, get her on the table.
Oh, my God.
What the hell? I'm so... I'm so...
That's tragic, man.
Go, go, go. Back door's clear.
Go! Go!
Get up, Marcus!
The gas got stuck.
I didn't mean to.
Oh, man.
Supple leather, you know?
You ever rub your leather?
You know, like, just rub it,
see how good it feels?
What does love
mean to you, Mike?
Don't worry about me
and my love.
Look, I got plenty of love
in my life.
Like a woman's butt.
Don't do that.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Mike.
Let's just concentrate
and get this warrant.
I need to express
right now...
I want you to know,
if this is our last job,
I really appreciate you.
Okay?
No, this is not gay shit.
This is man shit.
You know what I mean?
And you a beautiful man.
You know?
And when you let
the beautiful side...
Wh...What?
Look at your pupils.
How am I look at
my pupil? What, I'm...
Yo, what are you taking?
Did you take some of that X?
Hey, look, give me a hug.
Hey, get off. Listen,
listen. Listen!
We need this warrant.
Do not fuck this up.
Pull yourself together.
Arr! Arr!
Evening, captain.
Hello...capteeon.
So, how do you two plan
to fuck up my evening tonight?
Well, captain, believe me,
we would not be here...
if it weren't seriously,
utterly important.
Get in here.
Get off me!
Ho, ho, ho, Cap,
this is beautiful.
Have such a warm feel,
you know?
Sort of like a ving shwa.
What's it, Mike?
Mike, it was a V,
like a von schwo.
Why don't you have a seat?
Or ven wangs, or...
Feng shui.
Von sway.
You have a von sway home.
Make yourself at home.
All right, captain,
I know you said that
Johnny Tapia was hands-off...
but, captain,
we got him. It's a wrap.
Look, we messed up today,
but we got him.
Please just look.
How do I move it?
Here, you can go flip
through the pictures.
You can flip...You can
flip through picture...
This is horrible.
Mike!
Take the picture.
You can look
really close, Cap.
Listen, we got everything
that we need
to take this dude.
Oh, God. Oh.
They're taking
the organs out.
Right there you can...
You can...
If you look there...
Oh, gosh. Oh.
Oh, this is good.
That's horrible.
[SNIFF]
Mm-mm.
Look at this.
Everybody just needs
to relax.
Whoosah. Whoosah. Whoosah.
What are you doing?
Marcus, it's 2 a.m.
Get your hands off me.
Oh...
Oh, remember we said
we were gonna...
call Vargas and Reyes?
No, I don't...
Call Vargas!
Tell him the thing
we said to tell him.
What thing?
Tell him we said...
About yesterday.
And tell him
about the thing.
So, captain, listen,
we've also got videotape.
Yesterday, we fucked up bad.
But we got him now.
Oh, shit.
What?
No, a lot of times
with these...
Oh, shit!
What? Did I erase it?
No. We got video.
We got fucking...
Oh. Let me see.
Oh, shit.
Captain, he's shipping
the drugs around the country
in dead bodies.
We found coffins full
of cash tagged for Cuba.
And you think Tapia's
about to move out
with all this money?
I love it when you
call me Bunny Nose.
Shit!
Yeah, I do, girl.
You should see this sexy shit
I got on.
Who the hell are you
talking to?
I talked to Vargas and...
Ru...Reyes.
They said that
they're down for whatever.
This is a nice fish, you know?
Big fucking eyes,
but a nice fucking fish.
We need this
warrant, captain.
Let's take this scumbag down.
What the fuck
is going on?
He, uh, ingested X.
You okay, pal?
Take it easy.
Okay, thank you.
Poison lady says we
gotta keep him cool.
Otherwise, he's burning up,
he can get brain damage.
Nobody'll even notice that.
Mike, I got an erection.
Ho...Take me home.
Hey...
Call the wife,
tell her I'm on the way.
[♪♪♪]
Hope you guys hear me.
We got her. Loud and clear.
She's in.
Showtime.
Palm Mortuary, Alpha team.
Tapia's mansion, Delta.
Dixie Boy boat dock, Bravo.
Coast Guard gunships,
anything that hits the water.
We hit all three places
simultaneously.
Tac up at 0845.
We go hot at 0900 sharp.
Bring the noise.
You're such a beautiful girl.
Thank you.
Johnny...
Yeah?
Is she a Negro?
Please, Mama!
Shut up!
Get out of here!
[IN SPANISH]
You make your bed,
you sleep in it!
You take risks. I like that.
Or...
maybe I'm the one taking
a risk on you. Huh?
Yeah?
Excuse me, boss.
We need to talk now.
Whoa, something's
going on outside.
Cops.
What the fuck
do you mean, cops?
Goddamn it.
Whoa. DEA. You guys aren't
planning on going in there,
are you?
Slow down, there, cowboy.
We have a warrant.
I've got a UC inside.
She's gotta come out first.
You got two minutes, my man.
Call her on her cell.
Yes, sir.
Cut the power to the house.
You got her?
No, sir.
Well, let's go.
We got a bogey
in front of the house.
God.
This is for you, Josef,
and me and Mother Russia.
They're not gangbanger
homeys, boss.
They're cops.
Cops?
They weren't trying
to hit the load.
I think they were
looking after her.
Now, you tell me...
where is the wire?
They made her.
We gotta get her out.
Go! Go! Come on!
Hey, Tapia, you fucking mother.
[GUNSHOTS]
The Russian Grim Reaper is here.
Everything's in here.
Oh, shit. Goddamn.
Eyeball, has anything
left this mortuary
in the past two hours?
A four-hearse
funeral just left.
We trailed them
to Miami Harbor.
Miami Air, Tapia's running
his money to Cuba.
Get us a chopper!
Hey, Tapia!
You scared of me,
you little scumbag?
We got some heat.
Pull the car back.
I'll fucking kill you!
Hey, who the hell are you?
Drop the weapon!
Drop the weapon now!
I'm with you guys!
Put it down, now!
I'm over here!
Shut up!
I'm with you!
I'll kill that son of a bitch!
This is Alpha.
Heads up to the Coast Guard
Sharks and Bravo Team.
Lock down the harbor.
Freeze any boat on the move.
This is Bravo.
We got a go-fast
slinging a high rate of speed
down Miami harbor.
Stop that boat.
This guy's moving us.
Think we're going
for the bridge.
Coast Guard, we're going in.
Miami Police.
Shut it down.
This is the police.
[IN SPANISH]
Watch out, he's got a weapon
onboard.
Bail out!
Coast Guard, take him down.
Burn him.
Vessel is dead in the water.
This is what we do.
Oh, man, it's full up.
It's full up.
It's a righteous bust.
How the hell they slip away?
Give me the watch commander
on the horn.
Do you know her brother
on Miami PD?
Find him.
Do you know anyone
who might want
to save your life?
Hmm?
[PHONE RINGING]
Hello?
Marcus, they...!
You have
$100 million of mine...
and I want it back
in 48 hours.
Shit just got real.
Jack Snell, DEA.
Agent Eames, FBI,
who has just
informed me
that satellite
has pinpointed Tapia's jet
in Cuban airspace
about 20 minutes ago.
Cuba?
The United States
does not negotiate
with any hostage-takers,
especially
Cuban hostage-takers.
It's a delicate situation.
This is not just a situation.
This is my sister.
Off the record,
all our agencies
in the State Department
are using all their
back-channel contacts
for a diplomatic solution.
You know, by the time
y'all finish being diplomatic...
my sister could be
in a fucking box.
This is bullshit.
He ain't getting away
from us that easy.
We ride together...
we die together.
Bad boys for life.
We just gotta do it ourselves,
man.
I don't know you.
You look like you're about
to do something stupid.
I'm in.
Dodd here tell you
how fucking crazy
us ex-Delta guys are?
Marcus, my brother,
Tito, lives in Cuba.
He's a little crazy,
but he's hooked up
with the underground.
Weapons, men, a safe house.
Whatever we need.
You can forget about passports,
baby, and all that stuff,
because if the Cubans catch us,
we're all dead.
My brother Tito's
in Alpha 66,
the Anti-Castro Underground.
What does that have to do
with Tapia?
Everything. Johnny Tapia's
the biggest supplier
of drug cash to Castro,
so Alpha 66 will be
all over him.
No, listen, brother,
that is perfect.
Hey, guys. He says he can get
men on the tunnel right away.
MIKE: Let me
holler at him.
Tito, we need layout, security,
the whole deal.
We got info that Tapia's
got a casket coming in
tomorrow at 4:00 p.m.
Yeah, that might be our way in.
Yeah.
CAPTAIN: Brought you
a little care package
from my friends over at the CIA.
They want to help...
and don't ask me.
They're spies.
Former Delta Intel and Demo,
requesting permission
to tag along.
Ronnie, I hear
there's a boat on fire
off the coast of Cuba.
Don't you think
we ought to break
international waters
to help them out?
That's my dawg.
Point of no return.
I want to thank y'all
from the bottom of my heart.
Mike, look, I just...
Tell me when we get back.
I got the target in sight.
I see the boat.
Roger. Target 12 o'clock.
300 yards.
Roper in the door. Stand by.
Go! Go! Go!
Tito?
Welcome to Cuba. Vamos.
Damn. What's up
with the safe house
right across the street
from Tapia's crib?
This is the last place
anyone would look.
We have been
watching the place.
Guards play soccer
every day around 3:30.
The bad news?
Everyone around here knows
he uses the army
like his own bodyguards.
This is Tapia's
compound.
Wow. CIA hooked us up, huh?
Yeah. This LIDAR
laser technology
even shows his escape tunnel.
The alarm security
is wired to the army,
so we're severely screwed
if we don't blow up
this security room
before we make a move.
The tunnel we're digging
branches off...
one under his backyard,
and the other into
his escape tunnel.
We gotta hurry up.
See? I told you my brother
was a maniac.
How we looking?
Let me check it out.
Papi, you look like Jesus.
Why they call this
The Last Supper?
It was the last time
they were all together
before Jesus was crucified.
Crucified?
Hold your ears.
Hey, you.
Listen to me.
This is fucking depressing!
You understand?
I mean, who had
this fucking idea?
I just want little angels
looking down on me.
Okay, here's the ocean,
300 yards from Tapia's house.
We're here. Safe house.
First tunnel
comes through to here.
First team's going to pop out
and take out
the security station.
Second tunnel comes through
into the center of the house.
Tito, your contacts inside
said Syd's in
the last bedroom
on the second floor,
right?
Lupe is one of us.
If she says
your sister's there...
she is there.
Three o'clock sharp,
the bag of cats and iguanas
go over the fence,
so hopefully,
they'll make the motion
detectors go so crazy
that security'll
just shut them off.
TITO: My guys will watch
the outside
for any military.
If they come, that's bad.
Let's make this count, guys.
We're in.
[ALARM SOUNDS]
Goddamn it, it's
the fifth time today.
Carlos, turn off
the motion sensors
till we get it fixed.
Papi, look what I found.
Can I keep them?
No.
All right, guys...
sensors are down.
Time to move.
We are 100% go.
Let's go.
Left. Left. Yeah. There we go.
There. This is not as easy
as it looks.
Okay, we're at the T.
Split right.
Good luck, guys.
Find the soccer game.
Sniff it out, baby.
Sniff it out.
To the left. To the left.
Oh, shit.
Oh, you did not see me.
You did not see me.
Ready to bust into
the escape tunnel.
There we go. Soccer.
Sorry.
[SPEAKING SPANISH]
Go, go, go, go, go!
Go!
Get me the American bitch.
Call General Santos.
Tell him I need him now!
Sorry, darling.
Take her outside to safety.
Come on.
Carlos, this is not good!
I know!
Where is General Santos?
He's coming.
He's coming, boss.
You fucking maricons!
I'm gonna blow your head off!
What's happened to this gun?
My son is going to slice you
into chorizo.
Mama, I'm very sorry.
You little puta!
Vargas, you in?
We got Mama and the girl.
We're entering the house. Go!
Move! Move! Move!
Everything's clear outside.
You got 30 seconds max.
Haul ass.
Be advised you got two rovers
on the balcony.
I can't get a shot off.
[GUNFIRE]
See the rover? I missed him!
I missed him!
Get down!
Get down now!
Get down! Down!
Move! Move! Move!
Marcus!
Come on!
Move! We got the package.
Okay, guys, you've
got to move now.
It's turning into
a real bad day.
Vargas, we're coming back.
Cover us!
We got you covered
right here, baby.
Somebody talk to me.
What's going on, guys?
The military is everywhere.
This is bad. I have to go.
Guys, listen, you have
a lot of company.
Get out of there now!
I'm hit! I'm hit!
Head for the tunnel.
I'll blow this thing!
Go, go! Get out!
Mike, Mike, please, man,
you gotta get out.
Vargas! Get out! Get out!
Abort!
We're not going to make it
to the tunnel! Go to plan B.
We're going to plan B!
What plan B?!
You don't pay attention to shit!
What's the plan B?
That's your goddamn problem!
Are you fucking shitting me?
Let's go!
You follow me! Follow me!
Plan B? What the hell
is plan B?
Tito, what you doing here?
You need a Cuban
guide, fool.
This way!
They're not going to
make it to the tunnel.
Let's blow out of here!
Keys, keys, keys!
Oh, my God! No! God!
Oh, my God!
Plan B did not have
that big-ass gun in it!
You call this plan B?!
What the plan B
stand for? Bullshit!
Do you want to drive?
Yeah, pull over
by the motherfuckers
with the machine guns!
Whoo!
Yeah!
I am not to be fucked with!
I guess I missed
the part of the meeting
when you drive through
the dining room?
And right out
the front door.
Get in the truck!
Cuban army was everywhere.
Gotta get us to
Guantanamo Bay, Tito!
No, no, no. You can't just drive
onto a U.S. Naval base.
Hey, we're Americans, okay?
Hey, Marcus, you know how
when we usually
get in these
situations,
I'm always trying to
make you feel better,
like we'll be all right,
like we're going to make it?
Yeah, yeah.
I could say it,
but that'd be a bunch
of bullshit today.
Military, military.
Which way?
No, right! Right!
Go right!
These are drug dealer shacks.
They make cocaine here.
A lot of shit in there
that likes to blow.
Faster! I'm gonna kill you,
motherfucker!
I'm gonna go for it.
This is a big-ass hill.
Oh, shit! Is this still
called plan B?
No, this is definitely plan C.
God! God!
All right, everybody start
shooting at somebody!
Shoot! Shoot!
Shit! I'm out!
I got two rounds left.
One in the chamber.
I'm out.
All these guns and none
of you got no bullets?
I got one in my hip!
Oh, God, he's hit!
There! Gitmo!
U.S. soil, baby. U.S. soil.
Come on! Go! Go!
[HONKING]
Americans on the way!
Run it! Run it!
Go!
Go! Go! Go!
Fuck.
Mike!
[NO AUDIO]
We're Americans!
I pay my motherfucking taxes!
Shoot them!
Hey, fucking gringo.
Drop the gun!
Put it down! Put it down!
They can't help you.
You're staying in Cuba.
[SHOUTING IN SPANISH]
You are standing
on a live minefield!
Do not move!
Look, why don't we all go home...
Well, we'll go home,
you go to a hotel.
Let's work this shit out
another day,
because none of us is having
a good day right now.
Give me the gun!
Okay. I'll toss it
right at your feet...
right next to the mine.
Now, that's how
you supposed to shoot!
From now on,
that's how you shoot!
Oh, I want my next partner
to shoot just like that.
It take
a dysfunctional motherfucker
to bust somebody in the head
like that.
That's some dysfunctional shit.
My next partner
gonna invite me to his barbecues
and shit, though.
Come here, girl. Come here.
I came all the way to Cuba
for this.
Come on.
Y'all gotta do that
around land mines?
Would you tell them that
that shit is dangerous
around these land mines?
[♪♪♪]
You know, Mike,
this ain't easy for me,
but I was wrong.
I'll be very proud for you
to date my sister.
Thanks, man.
All right.
You know, me and Syd
thought about it,
and your behavior was so crazy
that whatever magic
we could've captured,
probably best if we didn't
even...you know.
Are you're just gonna
take advantage
of my little sister?
Already you breaking her heart?
What you talking about?
What, she not good
enough for you, Mike?
Syd, Mike says
you ain't shit!
Now, why would you scream out
some crazy nonsense like that?
You know, I don't appreciate
you coming over here,
disrespecting me in my new pool.
I bought your new pool.
Why don't you hook this pool up
to your Ferrari
and drag this motherfucker
out of here?
First of all, I was joking
with you.
And second of all,
all this right here,
smell yourself right now,
because this moment is
what the fuck is wrong with you.
I got the transfer papers
in the trash can.
I'll get them and glue them
the fuck up.
Glue them up, Marcus.
You want some glue?
Then we won't be partners
no more.
I got glue in the car.
I'm trying to talk to you.
It's hot, I feel like
I'm cooking in this fucker...
and I gotta hear
some shit out of you?
And on top of that shit,
you gonna dawg my baby sister?
Oh, this that bullshit!
Dad! Dad!
I kept the warranty.
I kept the warranty!
♪ Bad boys, bad boys
What you gonna do? ♪
♪ What you gonna do
When we come for you? ♪
♪ Mucka tyze stickm no
Hey ♪
♪ Bad boys, bad... ♪
♪ ...hey ♪
Come on, man, you gotta
learn the words.
Mike, you don't know
the damn words either.
♪ Bad boys, bad boys
What you gonna do? ♪
♪ What you gonna do
When they come for you? ♪
♪ Bad boys, bad boys
What you gonna do? ♪
♪ What you gonna do
When they come for you? ♪♪
[♪♪♪]
♪ Uh! ♪
♪ Nigga, what? Nigga, huh? ♪
♪ Shoot 'em up, bang, bang
Yeah, it's a cold thang ♪
♪ Diddy want Doggy to get
In my baby body man ♪
♪ Diddy got it, man
Tryin' a feel up his body man ♪
♪ With a lot of thing
Fuck the nigga home ♪
♪ A matter fact
He gettin' potty trained ♪
♪ Livin' with his mama, man ♪
♪ Stressed and pain, no gain ♪
♪ No fame, for a nigga
Like the D-O ♪
♪ Put a couple holes
In your loud mouth zero ♪
♪ If you step to us
You'll get fucked up quick ♪
♪ We can protect what us
That what we bustin' bitch ♪
♪ Niggaz be talkin' shit
But they be walkin' away ♪
♪ When I pull out my nine
And pop some times ♪
♪ When you see my clique in this
Bitch we kickin' it ♪
♪ Dogg's be rippin' this
Slip a clip in it ♪
♪ Flip the script
And then ♪
♪ I'm the rap nigga
Bangin' that here ♪
♪ And you don't quit ♪
♪ Ride to the rhythm
With some gangster shit ♪
♪ And you don't stop ♪
♪ Nigga, what? Nigga, huh? ♪
♪ And you don't quit ♪
♪ Ride to the rhythm
With some gangsta shit ♪
♪ And you don't stop ♪
♪ Nigga, what? Nigga, huh? ♪
♪ Nigga, what?
Doggystyle, Bad Boy ♪
♪ And you don't quit ♪
♪ Ride to the rhythm
With some gangsta shit ♪
♪ And you don't stop ♪♪
♪ Baby don't, don't go ♪
♪ You know I need you so ♪
♪ Sometimes my pride
Gets in the way ♪
♪ I say things
That I don't mean ♪
♪ When I think
You're hurting me ♪
♪ I love you more and more
Each day, each day ♪
♪ I didn't, I didn't mean
To make you cry ♪
♪ I don't want, I don't want you
To say goodbye ♪
♪ I didn't, I didn't mean
To make you sad ♪
♪ You're the best love
I've ever had ♪
♪ And nothin', nothin's gonna
Tear us apart ♪
♪ And for this
For this love we work so hard ♪
♪ And can we, can we try
To work it out ♪
♪ I'm yours all yours
Without a doubt ♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♪ Oh ♪♪
[♪♪♪]