Yes, Marlin.
I see it. It's beautiful.
So, Coral, when you said
you wanted an ocean view,
you didn't think you were going
to get the whole ocean, did you?
Oh, yeah!
A fish can breathe out here.
Did your man deliver or did he deliver?
- My man delivered.
- It wasn't so easy.
A lot of clownfish
had their eyes on this place.
You better believe they did.
Every single one of them.
You did good
and the neighbourhood is awesome.
- So you do like it, don't you?
- No, no, I really do like it.
But, Marlin, I know that
the Drop Off is desirable,
great schools, amazing view,
but do we really need so much space?
Coral, honey,
these are our kids we're talking about.
They deserve the best.
Look. They'll wake up, poke their
little heads out and see a whale
right by their bedroom window!
- You're going to wake the kids.
- Oh, right. Right.
Look.
They're dreaming.
- We still have to name them.
- All of them? Right now?
All right. We'll name this half Marlin Jr.
and this half Coral Jr.
- Okay, we're done.
- I like Nemo.
Nemo?
We'll name one Nemo,
but I'd like most of them to be Marlin Jr.
In a couple of days,
we're going to be parents!
Yeah.
- What if they don't like me?
- Marlin...
There's over 400 eggs.
Odds are one of them
is bound to like you.
What?
- You remember how we met?
- I try not to.
Well, I remember.
Excuse me, miss.
Can you see if I have a hook in my lip?
- Marlin.
- Look closer.
- Get away!
- Here he is. Cutie's here!
Where did everybody go?
Coral, get inside the house.
No, don't. They'll be fine.
Just get inside.
You. Right now.
No!
Coral!
Coral?
There, there.
It's okay. Daddy's here.
Daddy's got you.
I promise I will never let
anything happen to you,
Nemo.
First day of school! Wake up!
Come on. First day of school.
I don't want to go to school.
- Not you, Dad. Me.
- Okay.
Get up! Time for school!
- All right, I'm up. It's time for school.
- Oh, boy!
Nemo!
- First day of school!
- Don't move.
You'll never get out of there yourself.
I'll do it.
- You feel a break?
- No.
Sometimes fluid is rushing to the area.
Any rushing fluids?
- No.
- How many stripes do I have?
- Answer the question.
- Three.
No! Something's wrong with you.
I have one, two...
Three. That's all I have?
You're okay. How's the lucky fin?
- Lucky.
- Let's see.
Sure you want to go to school this year?
- You can wait five or six years.
- Come on, Dad. It's time for school.
Forgot to brush.
Do you want this anemone to sting you?
- Yes.
- Brush.
- I'm done.
- You missed a spot.
- Where?
- There.
Right there. And here and here.
We're excited. First day of school.
Here we go. We're ready to learn.
What do we have to remember
about the ocean?
- It's not safe.
- That's my boy.
First, we check to see that the coast
is clear. We go out and back in.
Then we go out and back in.
Then one more time. Out and back in.
- If you want to do it four times...
- Dad...
All right. Come on, boy.
Maybe while I'm at school,
I'll see a shark.
- I doubt that.
- Have you ever met a shark?
- No, and I don't plan to.
- How old are sea turtles?
Sea turtles? I don't know.
Sandy Plankton from next door said that
sea turtles live to be
about 100 years old.
If I ever meet a sea turtle, I'll ask him,
after I'm done talking to the shark.
Hold on. Wait to cross.
Hold my fin. Hold my fin.
You're not going to freak out
like you did at the petting zoo.
That snail was about to charge.
I wonder where we're supposed to go.
- Bye, Mom.
- I'll pick you up after school.
Come on, you guys.
Stop it. Give it back.
Come on. We'll try over there.
Excuse me.
Is this where we meet his teacher?
- Look who's out of the anemone.
- Yes, shocking, I know.
- Marty?
- Marlin.
- Bob.
- Ted.
Phil. Hey, you're a clownfish.
You're funny, right? Tell us a joke.
- Yeah.
- Good idea.
That's a misconception. Clownfish are
no funnier than any other fish.
- Come on, Clowny.
- Do something funny.
All right. I know one joke.
There's a mollusk. He walks up to...
Well, he swims up.
Actually, the mollusk isn't moving.
He's in one place.
And then the sea cucumber...
I'm mixed up. There was
a mollusk and a sea cucumber.
None of them were walking...
Sheldon!
Get out of Mr Johanssen's yard now!
All right, you kids!
Where'd you go? Where'd you go?
Can I go play, too? Can I?
I would feel better if you go play
over on the sponge beds.
That's where I would play.
- What's wrong with his fin?
- He looks funny.
- Hey, what did I do?
- Be nice. It's his first time at school.
He was born with it.
We call it his lucky fin.
Dad...
See this tentacle?
It's shorter than all my other tentacles.
But you can't really tell.
Especially when I twirl them like this.
I'm H20 intolerant.
I'm obnoxious.
Let's name the zones,
the zones, the zones
Let's name the zones of the open sea
Mr Ray!
- Come on, Nemo.
- Stay with me.
There's epipelagic, mesopelagic,
bathyal, abyssopelagic
All the rest are too deep
for you and me to see
I wonder where my class has gone.
We're under here.
There you are! Come aboard, explorers.
Knowledge exploring is oh so lyrical
When you think thoughts
that are empirical
Dad, you can go now.
- Well, hello. Who is this?
- I'm Nemo.
Nemo, all new explorers
must answer a science question.
- Okay.
- You live in what kind of home?
In an anemoninny.
Anemonemenemone.
Don't hurt yourself. Welcome aboard.
Just so you know, he's got a little fin.
If he's having trouble swimming,
let him take a break. 15 minutes.
Dad, it's time for you to go now.
We're going to stay together.
Okay, class. Optical orbits up front.
Remember, we keep our
supraesophageal ganglion to ourselves.
- That means you, Jimmy.
- Oh, man!
- Bye, Nemo.
- Bye, Dad.
Bye, son.
Be safe.
You're doing well for a first-timer.
You can't hold on to them forever,
can you?
I had a tough time when
my eldest went out on the Drop Off.
The Drop Off!
They're going to the Drop Off?
Are you insane?
Why don't we fry them up now
and serve them with chips?
Hey, Marty, calm down.
Don't tell me to be calm, pony-boy.
Pony-boy?
For a clownfish,
he really isn't that funny.
Pity.
Let's name the species,
the species, the species
Let's name the species
that live in the sea
Mollusca and gastropoda, arthropoda,
echinoderma, chordata
And some fish like you and me!
Come on. Sing with me.
Seaweed is cool, seaweed is fun
It makes its food
from the rays of the sun
Okay, the Drop Off.
All right, kids.
Feel free to explore, but stay close.
Stromatolitic cyanobacteria! Gather.
An ecosystem contained
in one infinitesimal speck.
Come on. Let's go.
Come on. Sing with me.
There's porifera, coelenterata,
hydrozoa, scyphozoa
Anthozoa, ctenophora, bryozoas three
Hey, guys, wait up.
Whoa!
Cool.
Saved your life!
You guys made me ink.
What's that?
I know what that is.
Sandy Plankton saw one.
He said it was called a butt.
Wow. That's a pretty big butt.
Look at me.
I'm going to go touch the butt.
Oh, yeah? Let's see you get closer.
Okay.
Beat that.
Come on, Nemo. How far can you go?
- My dad says it's not safe.
- Nemo, no!
Dad?
You were about to
swim into open water.
No!
Good thing I was here.
- He wasn't going to go.
- He was too afraid.
- I wasn't.
- This does not concern you.
You're lucky I don't tell your parents.
You can't swim well.
- I can swim fine, Dad, okay?
- No. It's not okay.
You shouldn't be near here.
You'll start school in a year or two.
No. Just because
you're scared of the ocean...
Clearly you're not ready.
You think you can do these things,
but you just can't!
I hate you.
There's...
Nothing to see. Gather there.
Anything I can do?
I am a scientist. Is there any problem?
I didn't mean to interrupt.
He isn't a good swimmer.
I think it's too soon
for him to be out here unsupervised.
I can assure you,
he's quite safe with me.
I'm sure he is.
But you have a large class
and he can get lost from sight
if you're not looking.
Oh, my gosh!
Nemo's swimming out to sea.
Nemo!
What do you think you're doing?
You're going to get stuck
and I'm going to have to get you
before another fish does.
Get back here.
I said get back here now!
Stop.
You take one more move, mister...
Don't you dare.
If you put one fin on that boat...
Are you listening to me?
Don't touch the boa...
Nemo!
He touched the butt.
You paddle your little tail back here.
That's right.
You are in big trouble, young man.
Do you hear me? Big...
Daddy, help me!
I'm coming, Nemo.
Get under me, kids.
No! Dad!
Nemo!
Nemo! Nemo, no!
Nemo, Nemo!
No!
Hold on!
Oh, no.
No. It's gone. It's gone.
It can't be gone. No. No!
Nemo! Nemo...
Nemo!
No.
Nemo! Nemo!
No. Please, no.
No, no.
Has anybody seen a boat?
Please. A white boat?
My son! My son!
Help me. Please.
Look out!
Sorry. I didn't see you, sir.
Are you okay?
- He's gone.
- There, there.
- It's all right.
- It'll be okay.
- No, they took him away.
I have to find the boat.
- A boat? I've seen a boat.
- You have?
- And it passed by not too long ago.
- A white one?
- Hi. I'm Dory.
- Where? Which way?
It went this way.
- Follow me.
- Thank you.
Thank you so much.
No problem.
Wait.
Quit it. I'm trying to swim here.
The ocean isn't big enough for you?
You got a problem, buddy?
Do you? Do you?
Want a piece of me? Yeah.
I'm scared now!
- Wait.
- Stop following me, okay?
What? You're showing me
which way the boat went.
A boat? I've seen a boat.
It passed by not too long ago.
It went this way. Follow me.
Wait a minute. What is going on?
You already told me
which way the boat was going.
I did? Oh, no.
If this is some kind of joke,
it's not funny and I know funny.
- I'm a clownfish.
- No, it's not. I'm so sorry.
See, I suffer from
short-term memory loss.
Short-term memory loss.
- I don't believe this.
- No.
I forget things almost instantly.
It runs in my family.
At least I think it does.
Where are they?
Can I help you?
Something's wrong with you. Really.
You're wasting my time.
I have to find my son.
Hello.
Well, hi!
Name's Bruce.
It's all right. I understand.
Why trust a shark, right?
So, what's a couple of bites like you
doing out so late?
Nothing. We're not even out.
Great.
Then how would you morsels like to
come to a little get-together I'm having?
- You mean like a party?
- Yeah, right. A party.
- What do you say?
- I love parties. That sounds like fun.
Parties are fun and it's tempting,
but we can't because...
Come on. I insist.
Okay. That's all that matters.
Look. Balloons. It is a party.
Mind your distance, though.
Those balloons can be a bit dodgy.
You wouldn't want one of them to pop.
Anchor! Chum!
There you are, Bruce. Finally.
- We got company.
- It's about time, mate.
We've gone through the snacks
and I'm starving.
We almost had to have
a feeding frenzy.
Let's get this over with.
Right then. The meeting has
officially come to order.
Let us all say the pledge.
I am a nice shark,
not a mindless eating machine.
If I am to change this image,
I must first change myself.
Fish are friends, not food.
Except stinking dolphins.
Dolphins!
Yeah, they think they're so cute.
Look, I'm a flipping little dolphin.
Let me flip for you. Ain't I something?
Today's meeting is step five:
Bring a Fish Friend.
- Do you all have your friends?
- Got mine.
- Hey there!
- How about you, Chum?
Well, I seem to have misplaced my
friend.
It's all right, Chum.
Help yourself to one of my friends.
Thanks, mate. A little chum for Chum.
I'll start the testimonies.
Hello. My name is Bruce.
Hello, Bruce.
It has been three weeks
since my last fish, on my honour,
or may I be chopped up
and made into soup.
- You're an inspiration to us.
- Amen.
- Right, then. Who's next?
- Pick me. Pick me.
The little sheila down the front.
Come on up here.
Hi. I'm Dory.
Hello, Dory.
And... Well, I don't think
I've ever eaten a fish.
- Hey, that's incredible.
- Good on you, mate!
I'm glad I got that off my chest.
Anyone else? How about you, mate?
What's your problem?
Me? I don't have a problem.
- Okay.
- Denial.
Just start with your name.
Okay. Hello.
My name is Marlin. I'm a clownfish.
- A clownfish? Really?
- Go on. Tell us a joke.
I love jokes.
I actually do know
one that's pretty good.
There was this mollusk
and he walks up to a sea cucumber.
Normally they don't talk,
but in a joke, everyone talks.
The sea mollusk
says to the cucumber...
Daddy!
Nemo!
- I don't get it.
- For a clownfish he's not that funny.
No, he's my son.
He was taken by these divers.
You poor fish.
- Humans. Think they own everything.
- Probably American.
There is a father
looking for his little boy.
What do these markings mean?
- I never knew my father.
- Come here.
- We're all mates here.
- I can't read human.
Then we've got to find a fish
that can read this. Look. Sharks!
- Guys.
- No, Dory.
- That's mine. Give it back.
- Cut it out.
I'm sorry. Are you okay?
You really clocked me there.
Am I bleeding?
Dory, are you oka...
That's good.
Intervention!
- Just a bite.
- You hold it together, mate.
- Fish are friends, not food.
- Food!
Dory, look out.
I'm having fish tonight.
Remember the steps, mate.
Just one bite.
G'day.
There's no way out.
There's got to be a way to escape.
- Who is it?
- Help me find a way out.
Sorry. You'll have to come back later.
We're trying to escape.
There's no way out.
There's got to be a way out.
Here's something. "Es-ca-pé."
I wonder what that means.
- It's spelled just like the word "escape."
- Let's go.
Here's Brucie!
- Wait a minute. You can read?
- I can read? That's right!
Then here. Read this now.
He doesn't mean it.
He never even knew his father.
Don't fall off the wagon.
Oh, no! It's blocked.
No, Bruce!
Sorry about... Bruce, mate.
He's really... A nice guy.
I need to get that mask.
You want that mask? Okay.
No, no, no, no!
Quick. Grab the mask.
Oh, no. Bruce.
What?
Swim away!
Is the party over?
Nice.
Dad!
Daddy?
Barbara.
Prep for his anterior crown,
would you, please?
- And I'll need more cotton rolls.
- All right.
Hello, little fella.
Beauty, isn't he?
I found that guy struggling for life
and I saved him.
Has that Novocain kicked in yet?
Bubbles!
- My bubbles.
- He likes bubbles.
Slow down, little fella.
There's nothing to worry about.
- He's scared to death.
- I want to go home.
Do you know where my dad is?
Your dad's probably
back at the pet store.
Pet store?
- Like I'm from Bob's Fish Mart.
- Pet Palace.
- Fish-O-Rama.
- Mail order.
eBay.
- Which one is it?
- I'm from the ocean.
The ocean. The ocean!
He hasn't been decontaminated yet.
Jacques!
Clean him!
Ocean.
Voilà. He is clean.
Wow. The big blue. What's it like?
Big and blue?
I knew it.
If there's anything you need,
ask your Auntie Deb. That's me.
If I'm not around you can always
talk to my sister, Flo. Hi. How are you?
Don't listen to anything my sister says.
She's nuts.
- Can't hear you, Peach.
- I said we got a live one.
- Yes!
- Boy, oh, boy.
- What have we got?
- Root canal.
It's not going to be pretty.
- Clamp installed?
- Yup.
- What did he use to open?
- Glidden drill. He favours that one.
I can't see, Flo.
- Schilder Technique.
- That's a Hedstrom file.
That's not a Hedstrom file.
That's a K-Flex.
It's got a teardrop cross section.
A Hedstrom.
- K-Flex!
- Hedstrom!
There I go. Little help. Over here.
I'll go deflate him.
All right. Go ahead and rinse.
The human mouth
is a disgusting place.
- Nigel.
- What did I miss?
- Root canal. A doozy.
- What did he use to open?
- Glidden drill.
- He favours it.
Hope he doesn't get surplus sealer
at the portal terminus.
- Hello. Who's this?
- New guy.
- The dentist took him off the reef.
- An outie.
From my neck of the woods?
Sorry if I took a snap at you.
Fish got to swim. Birds got to eat.
No, no. Those aren't your fish.
They're my fish. Come on. Go. Shoo.
The picture broke.
This here's Darla. She's my niece.
Going to be eight this week.
Hey, little fella.
Say hello to your new mummy.
She's going to be here Friday
to pick you up.
You're her present.
It's our little secret.
Well, Mr Tucker,
while that sets up, I'm going to
go see a man about a wallaby.
Darla!
- What's wrong with her?
- She wouldn't stop shaking the bag.
- Poor Chuckles.
- He was her present last year.
Hitched a ride on the porcelain express.
She's a fish killer.
I can't go with that girl.
I have to get back to my dad.
- Daddy! Help me!
- He's stuck.
Nobody touch him.
Can you help me?
No. You got yourself in there,
you can get yourself out.
- Gill...
- I just want to see him do it, okay?
Calm down. Alternate wiggling
your fins and your tail.
I can't. I have a bad fin.
Never stopped me.
Just think about what you need to do.
Come on.
Perfect.
- You did it.
- Good squirming.
Wow, from the ocean!
Just like you, Gill.
Yeah.
I've seen that look before.
What are you thinking about?
I'm thinking tonight we give
the kid a proper reception.
- So, kid, you got a name or what?
- Nemo.
I'm Nemo.
Nemo.
You going to eat that?
Careful of that hammer.
- Dory!
- Sea-Monkey has my money.
Wake up. Get up.
- Come on.
- Yes, I'm a natural blue.
- Get up!
- Look out. Sharks eat fish!
Wow. Dusty.
The mask. Where's the mask?
No! The mask! Get it!
Get the mask! Get it!
Keeps going on, doesn't it?
Echo! Echo!
- What are you doing?
- I've lost the mask.
- Did you drop it?
- You dropped it!
That was my only chance of
finding my son. Now it's gone.
Hey, Mr Grumpy Gills.
- When you're down, know what to do?
- I don't want to know.
Just keep swimming.
Just keep swimming,
swimming, swimming
What do we do? We swim
Dory, no singing.
I love to swim
And when you want to swim
you want to...
I'm going to get stuck with that song.
It's in my head!
Sorry.
- See anything?
- Something's got me!
- That was me. Sorry.
- Who's that?
Who could it be? It's me.
Are... Are you my conscience?
Yeah. I'm your conscience.
We haven't spoken for a while.
How are you?
- Can't complain.
- Good.
Now, Dory, I want you to tell me,
do you see anything?
I see a...
- I see a light.
- A light?
Yeah. Over there.
Hey, conscience, am I dead?
I see it, too.
What is it?
It's so pretty!
I...
I'm feeling happy.
Which is a big deal for me.
I want to touch it.
Hey, come back. Come on back here.
I'm going to get you.
I'm going to swim with you
I'm going to be your best friend
Good feeling's gone.
I can't see.
I don't know where I'm going.
- The mask!
- What mask?
Okay. I can't see a thing.
Whoa, geez.
- Look. A mask.
- Read it!
I'm sorry, but if you could bring it
a little closer. I need the light.
That's great. Keep it right there.
- Just read it!
- Okay, okay.
Mr Bossy.
"P." Okay. P.
"Sher..."
P. Sher... P. Shirley...
P not Shirley.
The first line's "P. Sherman."
"P. Sherman" doesn't make any sense!
Second line.
"42..."
Light, please.
"Walla... Wallaby."
The second line's "42 Wallaby Way."
Just finish up. Speed read.
No pressure.
There's a lot of pressure!
Take a guess, with pressure.
- Sydney. It's Sydney!
- Duck!
I'm dead. I'm dead.
I died. I'm dead.
We did it, we did it
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah
No eating here tonight,
eating here tonight
No eating here tonight
You're on a diet
Dory. What did it say?
What did the mask say?
P. Sherman, 42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
I remembered what it said!
I forget things, but I remembered it.
- P. Sherman...
- Where is that?
I don't know. But who cares?
I remembered.
P. Sherman, 42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
I remembered it again!
Nemo.
Nemo!
Follow me.
State your name.
Nemo.
Brother Bloat, proceed.
Nemo, newcomer of orange and white.
You have been called forth to the
summit of Mount Wannahockaloogie
to join with us
in the fraternal bonds of tankhood.
- We want you in our club, kid.
- Really?
If you are able to swim through
the Ring of Fire!
Turn on the Ring of Fire.
You said you could do it.
The Ring of Fire!
Bubbles. Let me...
Isn't there another way? He's just a boy.
From this moment on,
you will now be known as Sharkbait.
Sharkbait!
Welcome, Brother Sharkbait.
Sharkbait.
- Enough with the Sharkbait.
- Sharkbait...
- Sharkbait's one of us now.
- Agreed.
We can't send him to his death.
Darla's coming in five days.
So what are we going to do?
I'll tell you.
We're going to get him out of here.
We'll help him escape.
- Escape? Really?
- We're all going to escape.
Not another one of your escape plans.
Sorry, but they never work.
Yeah, why should this be any different?
- 'Cause we've got him.
- Me?
- You see that filter?
- Yeah.
You're the only one who can
get in and out of that thing.
We need you to take a pebble
inside there and jam the gears.
You do that and this tank's going to
get filthier by the minute.
Soon the dentist
will have to clean the tank.
When he does, he'll take us out of
the tank, put us in individual baggies,
then we'll roll down the counter,
out of the window,
off the awning, into the bushes,
across the street and into the harbour.
It's foolproof.
- Who's with me?
- I.
I think you're nuts.
No offence, kid,
but you're not the best swimmer.
He's fine. He can do this.
So, Sharkbait, what do you think?
Let's do it!
P. Sherman, 42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
Where are you going?
To P. Sherman,
42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
If you ask where I'm going, I'll tell you.
P. Sherman, 42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
Where? I'm sorry. I didn't hear you.
Excuse me. Excuse me.
Hi. Do you know how to get... Hello?
Wait. Can you tell me... Hey!
Hold it!
Wait a minute. I'm trying to talk to you.
Okay, fellas. Come back here.
One quick question. I need to...
And they're gone again.
P. Sherman, 42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
Why do I have to tell you again?
- I don't get tired of it.
- All right, here's the thing.
I think it's best
if I carry on from here by...
- By myself.
- Okay.
You know. Alone.
Without... Well, not without you,
but I don't want you with me.
I don't want to hurt your feelings.
- You want me to leave?
- Well, not... Yes. Yeah.
I just can't afford any more delays.
You're one of
those fish that cause delays.
Sometimes it's a good thing.
There's a group of fish.
- They're delay fish.
- You mean...
- You mean you don't like me?
- Of course I like you.
Because I like you
I don't want to be with you.
It's a complicated emotion.
Don't cry. I like you.
Hey, you!
Lady, is this guy bothering you?
- I don't remember. Were you?
- No, no. We're just...
Do you guys know how I can get...
We're talking to the lady, not you.
You like impressions?
Okay.
Just like in rehearsals, gentlemen.
What are we? Take a guess.
- I've seen one of those.
- I'm a fish with a nose like a sword.
- Wait.
- It's a swordfish.
Hey, clown-boy, let the lady guess.
Where's the butter?
- It's on the tip of my tongue.
- Lobster.
- Saw that.
- What?
- Lots of legs.
- Clam?
Close enough.
It's a whale of a tale I'll tell you, lad
- They're good.
- Somebody give me directions?
"Would somebody give me directions?"
- I'm serious.
- Blah, blah, me, me.
Blah, blah, blah, me, me.
Thank you.
Oh, dear. Hey, come back.
What's the matter?
While they're doing impressions,
I am miles from home
with a fish that can't even
remember her own name.
- I bet that's frustrating.
- My son is out there.
- Your son Chico?
- Nemo.
It doesn't matter. 'Cause no fish
in this ocean is going to help me.
I'm helping you.
Wait right here.
- Guys.
- Is he bothering you again?
No, he's a good guy.
Go easy on him.
He's lost his son Fabio.
Heard of P. Sherman,
42 Wallaby Way, Sydney?
Sydney? Oh, sure.
Ted here's got relatives in Sydney.
Don't you, Ted?
- Sure do.
- Hey, they know Sydney!
- You wouldn't know how to get there?
- Follow the EAC.
That's East Australian Current.
Big current. You can't miss it. It's in
that direction.
Then you got to follow that for about...
What do you guys think?
Three leagues?
That baby's going to
float you right past Sydney.
Great! That's great!
- Dory, you did it.
- Oh, please.
I'm just your little helper. Helping along.
- Fellas, thank you.
- Don't mention it.
Just loosen up. Okay, buddy?
You guys! You really nailed him. Bye.
- Ma'am. One more thing.
- Yes?
When you come to this trench,
swim through it, not over it.
Trench. Through it.
Not over it. I'll remember.
Hey!
Wait up, partner. Hold on.
Wait. I've got to tell you something.
Whoa.
Nice trench.
Hello!
- Let's go.
- No, no. Bad trench. Bad trench.
- We're going to swim over this thing.
- Little red flag going up.
Something's telling me
we should swim through it.
Are you looking at this thing?
It's got death written on it.
I'm sorry, but I think
we should swim through.
I'm done talking about this. Over we go.
Come on. Trust me on this.
- Trust you?
- Yes. Trust. It's what friends do.
- Something shiny!
- Where?
- It just swam over the trench. Come on.
- Okay.
- Boy, it sure is clear up here.
- Exactly.
And look at that.
There's the current.
We should be there in no time.
- Hey, little guy.
- You wanted to go through the trench.
I shall call him Squishy and
he shall be mine. Come here, Squishy.
Come here, little Squishy.
- That's a jellyfish!
- Bad Squishy.
Shoo! Get away.
- Let me see.
- Don't touch it.
I'm not going to touch it.
I just want to look.
How come it didn't sting you?
It did. Hold still.
I live in this anemone and I'm used to
these kind of stings. Come here.
You're going to be fine.
But now we know
that we don't want to touch these again.
Let's be thankful it was just a little one.
Don't move.
This is bad, Dory.
- Boing. Boing.
- Dory!
You can't catch me.
Don't bounce on the tops. They will
not sting you!
- The tops don't sting you.
- Two in a row. Beat that.
Listen to me. I have an idea.
- A game.
- A game?
I love games. Pick me.
Here's the game. Whoever can hop
the fastest out of these jellyfish wins.
- Okay!
- Rules.
Don't touch the tentacles. Only the tops.
Something about tentacles. Got it.
On your mark. Get set. Go!
Wait!
Go faster if you want to win.
- Dory!
- Boing, boing, boing!
Wait a minute.
So, we're cheating death now.
We're having fun at the same time.
I can do this. Just be careful.
Careful I don't make you cry when I win.
I don't think so!
Give it up. You can't fight evolution.
I was built for speed.
- The question is, are you hungry?
- Hungry?
Yeah. 'Cause you're about to
eat my bubbles!
Duck to the left, back
and coming over, right there!
The clownfish is the winner!
We did it. Look at us!
Dory?
Oh, no.
Dory! Dory! Dory!
Dory!
Am I disqualified?
You're doing fine. You're winning.
Stay awake.
Where does P. Sherman live?
P. Sherman, Wallaby Way, Sydney.
That's it!
Stay awake. Stay awake. Stay awake.
Stay awake!
- Awake...
- P. Sherman...
- 42 Wallaby Way...
- Wake up.
- Sydney.
Nemo...
You miss your dad,
don't you, Sharkbait?
Yeah.
Well, you're lucky to have someone
out there who's looking for you.
He's not looking for me.
He's scared of the ocean.
Peach? Any movement?
He's had four cups of coffee.
It's got to be soon.
Keep on him.
My first escape, landed on dental tools.
- I was aiming for the toilet.
- The toilet?
All drains lead to the ocean, kid.
Wow. How many times
have you tried to get out?
I've lost count. Fish aren't meant to be
in a box, kid. It does things to you.
The bubbles, the bubbles!
Potty break! He just grabbed the
Reader's Digest. We have 4.2 minutes.
That's your cue.
- You can do it, kid.
- We got to be quick.
Once you get in, swim to the bottom
and I'll talk you through the rest.
Okay.
Go on. It'll be a piece of kelp.
- Nicely done. Can you hear me?
- Yeah.
Here comes the pebble.
Now, do you see a small opening?
Okay. Inside it you'll see a rotating fan.
Very carefully, wedge that pebble
into the fan to stop it turning.
Careful, Sharkbait.
- I can't do it.
- This isn't a good idea.
He'll be fine. Try again!
Okay.
That's it, Sharkbait.
Nice and steady.
- I got it, I got it!
- He did it.
That's great, kid.
Now swim up the tube and out.
Oh, no! Gill!
Sharkbait! Get him out of there!
- Help him!
- What do we do?
- Oh, no!
- Stay calm, kid. Just don't panic.
- Help me!
- Sharkbait, grab hold of this.
No!
- Feed me more.
- That's it!
Come on, Sharkbait. Grab it.
- I got it.
- Pull!
Gill, don't make him go back in there.
No. We're done.
Dude?
Focus, dude.
He lives. Hey, dude.
- What happened?
- I saw the whole thing, dude.
First you were all, like, whoa!
And then we were all, like, whoa!
- Then you were, like, whoa...
- What are you talking about?
You, mini-man! Taking on the jellies.
You got serious thrill issues, dude.
Awesome.
Oh, my stomach.
Man, no hurling on the shell.
I just waxed it.
- So, Mr Turtle...
- Dude, Mr Turtle is my father.
Name's Crush.
Crush? Really?
Okay, Crush.
Listen, I need to get to
the East Australian Current.
EAC?
Dude...
You're riding it, dude.
Check it out.
Okay, grab shell, dude.
Grab what?
Righteous! Righteous!
So,
what brings you on this fine day
to the EAC?
Well, Dory and I need to get to Sydney.
Dory! Is she all right?
Oh, little blue.
She is sub-level, dude.
Dory, Dory! Dory!
Oh, Dory.
I'm so sorry.
This is all my fault. It's my fault.
...twenty-nine, 30!
Ready or not, here I come!
There you are.
Catch me if you can.
Up you go!
Oh, my goodness.
Kill the motor, dude.
Let us see what Squirt does flying solo.
Whoa! That was so cool.
Hey, Dad. Did you see that?
Did you see me?
- Did you see what I did?
- You so totally rock, Squirt.
Give me some fin.
Noggin.
Dude.
Intro. Jellyman, Offspring.
Offspring, Jellyman.
- Jellies? Sweet.
- Totally.
I must have done
something you all liked, dudes.
You rock, dude.
Curl away, my son.
It's awesome, Jellyman.
When the little dudes are eggs
we leave them on a beach to hatch,
and coo-coo-cachoo, they find
their way back to the big ol' blue.
- All by themselves?
- Yeah!
But, dude, how do you know
when they're ready?
You never really know, but when
they know, you'll know. You know?
- Hey, look, everybody.
- I know that dude.
It's the Jellyman.
- Well go on. Jump on him.
- Turtle pile!
Wait. Kids!
- You funny?
- Where's your shell?
- Do your stripes come off?
- I need to breathe.
Did you cross the jellyfish forest?
- One at a time.
- Mr Fish, did you die?
Sorry. I was vague on the details.
- So where are you going?
- You see, my son was taken.
My son was taken away from me.
- No way!
- What happened?
No, kids. I don't want to talk about it.
- Come on.
- Please.
Well, okay.
I live on this reef, a long way from here.
This is going to be good. I can tell.
My son, Nemo, he was mad at me.
Maybe he wouldn't have done it
if I hadn't been so tough on him.
I don't know.
He swam in the open water to this boat
and these divers appeared
and I tried to stop them.
The boat was too fast,
so we swam out in the ocean...
He couldn't stop them.
Then Nemo's dad,
he swims out to the ocean
and they bump into three sharks.
He scares them away
by blowing them up.
- That's amazing.
- Then dives thousands of feet...
Straight into the dark. It's wicked
dark there. You can't see a thing.
The only thing
they can see down there is...
This big, horrible creature with
razor-sharp teeth! Nice parry.
Then he has to blast his way...
These fish have been
searching the ocean for days
on the East Australian Current.
He may be on his way here right now.
That should put him
in Sydney Harbour...
In a few days.
This guy will stop at nothing...
...stop at nothing until he finds his son.
I hope he makes it.
That's one dedicated father,
if you ask me.
Mine. Mine. Mine.
Would you just shut up?
- You're rats with wings.
- This bloke's looking for his boy, Nemo.
- He was taken off the reef by divers...
- There. Take it.
Say that again.
You said something about Nemo.
Mine. Mine. Mine.
Mine.
Last I heard,
he's heading towards the harbour.
Brilliant!
Is he doing okay?
I don't know, but whatever you do,
don't mention D-A-R...
It's okay.
I know who you're talking about.
Gill?
Hey, Sharkbait.
- I'm sorry I couldn't stop...
- I'm the one who should be sorry.
I was so ready to get out,
so ready to taste that ocean,
I was willing to put you
in harm's way to get there.
Nothing should be worth that.
I'm sorry I couldn't get you
back to your father, kid.
All right. Hey, hey, hey!
What the...
Well, that's one way to pull a tooth.
Darn kids. Well, good thing
I pulled the right one, eh?
Nigel, you just missed an extraction.
Has he loosened
the periodontal ligament yet?
What am I talking about?
Where's Nemo?
I've got to speak with him.
Your dad's been fighting the ocean
looking for you.
My father? Really?
He's travelled hundreds of miles.
- He's been battling sharks and jellyfish.
- Sharks?
- That can't be him.
- Are you sure? What was his name?
Some sort of sport fish. Tuna? Trout?
- Marlin?
- That's it.
- The clownfish from the reef.
- It's my dad! He took on a shark!
- I heard he took on three.
- Three?
- Three sharks?
- That's 4,800 teeth!
After you were taken by Diver Dan,
your dad followed the boat
like a maniac.
Really?
He's giving it all he's got
and then three sharks capture him.
He blows 'em up
and then dives thousands of feet
and gets chased
by a monster with huge teeth!
He ties this demon to a rock.
And his reward?
He gets to battle a jellyfish forest.
Now he's with sea turtles
on the East Australian Current
and the word is he's headed this way,
right now, to Sydney!
- What a good daddy.
- He was looking for you after all.
- He's swimming in the filter!
- Not again!
Sharkbait!
- No!
- You've got your life ahead of you.
- We'll help you.
- Get him out.
- Get him out of there.
- Come on. Grab the end.
Are you okay?
Can you hear me, Sharkbait?
Nemo? Can you hear me?
Yeah, I can hear you.
Sharkbait, you did it!
Sharkbait, you're...
Covered with germs!
That took guts.
All right, we have less than
48 hours before Darla gets here.
This tank will get plenty dirty
in that time,
but we have to help it along.
- Jacques, no cleaning.
- I shall resist.
Everybody else,
be as gross as possible.
Think dirty thoughts.
We're going to make this tank so filthy,
the dentist'll have to clean it.
Good work.
All right, we're here, dudes.
Get ready! Your exit's coming up, man.
- Where? I don't see it.
- Right there. I see it. I see it.
- You mean the swirling vortex of terror?
- That's it, dude.
- Of course it is.
- First, find your exit buddy.
- Do you have your exit buddy?
- Yes.
Squirt here will now give you a rundown
on proper exiting technique.
Good afternoon. We're going to have
a great jump today.
Crank a hard cutback
as you hit the wall.
There's a screaming bottom turn,
so watch out.
Remember, rip it, roll it and punch it!
It's like he's trying to speak to me,
I know it.
You're really cute, but I don't know what
you're saying. Say the first thing again.
Okay, Jellyman. Go, go, go!
- Whoa!
That was fun.
I actually enjoyed that.
Hey, look! Turtles.
Most excellent.
Now, turn your fishy tails round and
swim straight on through to Sydney.
No worries, man.
No worries. Thank you, Dude Crush.
- Bye.
- See you, Jellyman.
Tell your little dude I said hi, okay?
- See ya later, dudes.
- Bye, everyone.
Nemo would have loved this.
Hey, Crush. I forgot. How old are you?
150, dude!
And still young. Rock on!
150. I got to remember that.
Whoa.
- We going in there?
- Yep.
P. Sherman, 42 Wallaby Way, Sydney?
Yep.
We're going to just swim straight.
Just keep swimming
Dory...
Boy, this is taking a while.
- Hey, how about we play a game?
- Okay.
Okay, I'm thinking of something orange.
- And it's small...
- It's me.
Right.
This one you'll never guess.
It's orange and small.
It's me.
All righty, Mr Smarty Pants.
It's orange and small
and white stripes...
Me. And the next one, just a guess, me.
Okay. That's just scary.
Wait. I've seen
this floating speck before.
That means we've passed it.
That means we're not going straight.
We got to get to the surface.
We'll figure it out there.
- Hey!
- What?
Relax. Take a deep breath.
Now, let's ask somebody for directions.
Fine. Who? The speck?
There's nobody here!
There has to be someone.
It's the ocean.
We're not the only two in here.
Let's see...
Okay, no one there.
Nope.
- There's somebody. Hey, excu...
- Dory!
I'm thinking of something mysterious.
It's a fish we don't know, and if we
ask it directions, it could ingest us.
What is it with men
and asking for directions?
Don't play the gender card.
Let's play the "let's not die" card.
- Want to get out of here?
- Of course.
How are we going to do that unless
we give it a shot and hope for the best?
- You don't fully understand.
- Trust me on this.
All right.
Excuse me? Little fella?
Hello.
Don't be rude. Say hi.
- His son Bingo...
- Nemo.
- ...was taken to...
- Sydney.
Sydney, yes.
It's really important
that we get there as fast as we can.
Can you help us out?
Come on, little fella. Come on.
Dory, I'm a little fella.
I don't think that's a little fella.
Big fella. Whale. Okay.
Maybe he only speaks whale.
We need
to find his son.
What are you doing?
Are you sure you speak whale?
Can you give us...
- Heaven knows what you're saying.
- ...directions?
- See, he's swimming away.
- Come back.
You've offended him.
Maybe a different dialect.
This is not whale.
You're speaking, like, upset stomach.
- Maybe I should try humpback.
- No, don't.
- You sound sick.
- Maybe louder, huh?
- Don't do that.
- Too much orca.
- Didn't that sound a little orca-ish?
- It sounds like nothing I've ever heard.
Just as well. He might be hungry.
Whales don't eat clownfish.
They eat krill.
- Swim away!
- Look. Krill!
Move, Dory! Move!
Look at that. Would you look at that?
Filthy. Absolutely filthy.
And it's all thanks to you, kid.
You made it possible.
Jacques, I said no cleaning.
I am ashamed.
Look. Scum angel.
Bubbles! I love the bubbles.
Flo? Has anybody seen Flo? Flo!
9:00, and cue dentist.
Barbara. Sorry I'm late.
Okay. Here we go.
Little Davey Reynolds.
- Walks to the counter, drops the keys...
- Bloat, that's disgusting.
Tastes pretty good to me.
Don't you realise
we are swimming in our own...
- Here he comes.
- What the...
Crikey. What a state.
Barbara, what's my earliest
appointment tomorrow?
- 10:00, love.
- Leave it open.
I've got to clean the fish tank
before Darla gets here.
- You hear that, Sharkbait?
- Yay! He's going to clean the tank!
Yeah, we're going to be clean!
Ready to see your dad?
Course you are.
I wouldn't be surprised if he's out there
in the harbour waiting for you right now.
Yeah.
Here comes a big one!
Come on. You got to try this.
- Will you just stop it?
- Why? What's wrong?
- We're in a whale. Don't you get it?
- A whale?
A whale! 'Cause you had to ask for help.
And now we're stuck here.
- A whale? You know, I speak whale.
- You're insane. You can't speak whale.
I have to get out. I have to find my son.
I have to tell him
how old sea turtles are!
Hey.
You okay?
There, there.
It's all right. It'll be okay.
No. It won't.
Sure it will. You'll see.
No. I promised him I'd never
let anything happen to him.
That's a funny thing to promise.
What?
You can't never let anything
happen to him.
Then nothing would
ever happen to him.
Not much fun for little Harpo.
- What's going on?
- Don't know. I'll ask him.
- What's...
- Dory.
...going
on?
- I think he says we've stopped.
- Of course we've stopped.
Stop trying to speak whale.
You're going to make things worse.
What is that noise?
Oh, no. Look what you did.
The water's going down.
It's going down!
- Really? You sure about that?
- Look. Already it's half-empty.
- I'd say it's half-full.
- Stop that. It's half-empty!
Okay, that one was a little tougher.
He either said we should go
to the back of the throat
or he wants a root beer float.
Of course he wants us to go there.
That's eating us!
How do I taste, Moby? Do I taste good?
Tell him
I'm not interested in being lunch.
- Okay. He's...
- Stop talking to him.
- What is going on?
- I'll check. What...
No. No more whale.
You can't speak whale.
Yes, I can.
No, you can't.
You think you can do these things,
but you can't, Nemo.
- Okay.
- Dory!
He says it's time to let go.
Everything's going to be all right.
How do you know?
How do you know something bad
isn't going to happen?
I don't!
We're alive!
Look. Syd-ney.
Sydney! Sydney.
Sydney again.
You were right. We made it!
We're going to find my son.
Thank you, sir.
Wow. I wish I could speak whale.
Now we find the boat that took him.
- Right.
- Come on. We can do this!
Morning. It's morning, everyone.
Today's the day. The sun is shining, the
tank is clean and we are getting out of...
The tank is clean.
The tank is clean!
But how?
Boss must have installed it
while we were sleeping.
- What are we going to do?
- What's it say, Peach?
I can't hear you, Peach.
The Aqua Scum 2003 is an all-purpose,
self-cleaning salt-water purifier
that extends
the life of your aquarium fish.
Stop it!
The Aqua Scum is programmed
to scan your tank every five minutes?
Scan? What does that mean?
Temperature 82 degrees,
pH balance normal.
Nice.
Curse you, Aqua Scum!
- That's it for the escape plan.
- Then what are we going to do about...
Darla!
Stay down, kid.
- False alarm.
- My nerves can't take much more.
What are we going to do
when that brat gets here?
- I'm thinking, I'm thinking.
- Help!
- Help me!
- Hold on. I'm coming.
Help me!
Swim down! Come on, kid. Swim down!
- Everybody jump in.
- Swim down!
What the...
Good work.
- Gill!
- Sharkbait!
- Roll, kid! Lean, kid! Roll!
- Go to the window.
That would have been a nasty fall.
- I don't want to go belly-up!
- Calm down, Nemo.
You won't go belly-up. I promise.
You're going to be okay.
Darla!
Do any of these boats
look familiar to you?
No, but the boat has to be here.
- We're going to find it.
- I'm totally excited.
- Are you excited?
- Dory, wake up. Come on.
Duck!
That's not a duck. It's a pelican!
No! I didn't come this far
to be breakfast.
Hey, Nigel. Would you look at that?
What?
Sun's barely up and Gerald's
had more than he can handle.
Yeah. Reckon somebody
ought to help the poor guy.
Well, don't everybody fly off at once!
All right, Gerald. What is it?
Fish got your tongue?
Love a duck!
I've got to find my son Nemo.
Nemo?
He's that fish that's been
fighting the whole ocean.
Hey, I know where your son...
Wait. Come back.
- Stop!
- Keep going. He's crazy.
I've got something to tell you.
Mine.
Okay. Don't make any sudden moves.
Hop inside my mouth if you want to live.
Hop into your mouth?
And how does that make me live?
- Mine?
- Because I can take you to your son.
Yeah, right!
No. I know your son. He's orange.
He's got a gimpy fin on one side.
- That's Nemo!
- Mine! Mine! Mine!
Fasten your seat belts!
Mine! Mine! Mine!
Everybody hold on!
Too loud. Too loud for me.
Twinkle, twinkle, little star
Find a happy place.
Find a happy place!
Darla, your uncle will see you now.
All right. Let's see those pearly whites.
I'm a piranha.
They're in the Amazon.
And a piranha's a fish.
Just like your present.
- I got a fishy!
- Oh, no.
Poor little guy.
- He's dead.
- Sharkbait!
Yay! Fishy, fishy, fishy!
Must have left your present
in the car, sweetie. I'll go and get it.
He's still alive!
Why is he playing dead?
He's going to
get flushed down the toilet.
He's going to get out of here.
- What a smart little guy.
- No, not the trash can!
Hey! I found his dad.
- Where's Nemo?
- Dentist!
- He's over there.
- What's a dentist?
- Get in there.
- I can't go in there.
Oh, yes you can. Charge!
What the...
Darla, sweetie, look out.
Hold still. Easy, easy.
Hold still!
It's all right. Nobody's going to hurt you.
Nemo.
- Oh, my goodness.
- Gotcha!
- Nemo!
- Daddy?
Out with you. And stay out!
- Fishy?
Fishy!
Wake up! Wake up!
- Oh, no!
- To the top
of Mount Wannahockaloogie.
Why are you sleeping?
- Hurry!
- Bloat!
Ring of Fire!
Fishy!
- Get it out!
- Crikey!
The animals have gone mad!
Get it out!
- Smack her in the head!
- Go, Gill, go!
There's a fish in my hair!
- Gill.
- Sharkbait.
Tell your dad I said hi.
Go get him.
He did it!
- I'm happy.
- Is he going to be okay?
Don't worry.
All drains lead to the ocean.
Fishy!
Daddy!
I'm... I'm so sorry.
Truly I am.
- Hey...
- Dory.
If it wasn't for you,
I never would have even made it here.
So thank you.
Hey, wait a minute.
Wait. Where are you going?
It's over, Dory. We were too late.
Nemo's gone.
I'm going home now.
No. No, you can't.
Stop!
Please don't go away. Please?
No one's ever stuck with me
for so long before.
And if you leave...
I remember things better with you.
Look.
P. Sherman, 42...
42...
I remember it. It's there. I know it is.
Because when I look at you, I can feel it.
And I look at you and I...
I'm home.
Please. I don't want that to go away.
I don't want to forget.
I'm sorry, Dory,
but I do.
- Manna from heaven.
- Sweet nectar of life.
Hey!
- This is our spot.
- Go on. Get out of here.
Hey, hey, hey.
Yeah, that's it.
Too right, mate!
I got a live one here!
- Have you seen my dad?
- Gotcha!
- Come back here.
- You let him go!
Dad!
No!
- Excuse me.
- No.
- Are you all right?
- I don't know where I am.
I don't know what's going on.
I think I lost somebody,
but I can't remember.
- It's okay.
- I can't remember.
I'm looking for someone, too.
We can look together.
- I'm Dory.
- I'm Nemo.
Nemo?
That's a nice name.
- Dad!
- Dad.
Wait a minute. Is it your dad or my dad?
My dad.
- Got it. Dad!
- Where are we anyway?
Dad!
Syl... Schai...
Sydney.
P. Sherman, 42 Wallaby Way, Sydney.
- Nemo!
- What?
It's you! Nemo!
Yes. I'm Nemo.
You're Nemo.
You were dead. I saw you.
And then... Here you are.
You're not dead.
And your father... Your father!
My father? You know my father?
Where is he?
He went this way. Quick!
Hey!
Have you seen an orange fish swim by?
- It looks like him.
- But bigger.
I saw him,
but I'm not telling you where he went.
And there's no way
you're going to make me.
Mine.
All right. I'll talk!
He went to the fishing grounds.
- Hey, look out.
- Sorry.
I'm just trying to get home.
Daddy!
- Nemo?
- Daddy!
Nemo?
- Dad!
- Nemo's alive!
Dory?
- Nemo!
- Daddy!
- Nemo! I'm coming, Nemo!
- Dad!
Nemo! Thank goodness.
It's all right, son. It's going to be okay.
Turn around!
You're going the wrong way.
- Look out!
- Move!
- Dory!
- Come on.
Help! Get us out!
No, no, no! Dory!
- Dad, I know what to do.
- Nemo, no!
We have to tell all the fish
to swim down together.
- Get out of there.
- This will work.
No, I am not going to lose you again.
There's no time.
It's the only way we can save Dory.
I can do this!
You're right. I know you can.
- Lucky fin.
- Now, go. Hurry!
Tell all the fish to swim down.
Well, you heard my son. Come on.
- Dory, you have to tell everybody to...
- Swim down together.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Swim down!
- Everybody swim down.
- Come on. You have to swim down.
Down! Swim down!
Swim down! Swim down!
Don't give up! Keep swimming!
Just keep swimming!
That's it!
It's working!
Keep swimming!
Just keep swimming!
- Come on, Dad!
- You're doing great, son.
- That's my dad.
- Let's get to the bottom.
Just keep swimming
Almost there. Keep swimming!
Keep swimming!
Hey!
Where's Nemo?
There!
Oh, no. Nemo!
Nemo?
It's okay. Daddy's here.
Daddy's got you.
- Daddy?
- Oh, thank goodness.
Daddy...
- I don't hate you.
- Oh, no, no, no.
I'm so sorry, Nemo.
Hey, guess what?
- What?
- Sea turtles...
I met one.
And he was 150 years old.
150?
Yep.
'Cause Sandy Plankton said
they only lived to be 100.
Sandy Plankton?
Think I would cross the ocean and
not know as much as Sandy Plankton?
He was 150! Not 100.
Who is this Sandy Plankton
that knows everything wrong?
Time for school! Time for school!
Get up! Let's go!
- I'm going to win.
- No, you're not.
- I did it.
- My own son beats me.
Climb aboard, explorers.
So then the sea cucumber looks over
at the mollusk and says,
"With fronds like these,
who needs anemones?"
Well, hello, Nemo. Who's this?
- Exchange student.
- I'm from the EAC, dude.
- Sweet.
- Totally.
Seriously, Marty, did you really do
all the things you say you did?
Pardon me.
Hello.
Don't be alarmed.
We wanted to make sure
our newest member got home safely.
- Thanks.
- We'll see you next week.
- Keep up with the programme, Dory.
- Remember, fish are friends.
Not food! Bye!
Hold on. Here we go.
Next stop, knowledge.
Bye, son. Have fun.
Bye, Dad.
Mr Ray, wait. I forgot something.
Love you, Dad.
I love you, too, son.
Dad? You can let go now.
Sorry.
Now go have an adventure.
Goodbye. See you later, dudes!
- Bye, Elmo.
- Nemo.
- Nemo. Bye, Nemo.
- See you after school, Dory.
Bye, Dad!
Bye, son.
Barbara.
I don't understand it.
Here this thing has a lifetime guarantee
and it breaks.
Had to clean the tank myself,
take the fish out, put 'em in bags and...
Where'd the fish go?
Come on, Peach!
You got it. That's it. You can do it.
That's the shortest red light
I've ever seen.
Come on, Peach.
Now what?