You're always sick.
You were sick when
you were my age.
Evening, sir.
Evening, Victor.
I didn't realise that
you're still here.
I'm just keeping
James company, sir.
If that's all right...
Very kind of you.
- Are you better, son?
- Still cold, father.
It's just a mild fever, you'll
be all right in the morning.
You always say that.
And you always pull
through, don't you?
Now... take your medicine.
Elizabeth.
Your father's drunk again.
You should help him home, Victor.
It's not my name
he's calling, sir.
- Father.
- Stay where you are, James.
Father.
I told you never
to come back here.
James...
There are things you
don't understand.
- Don't...
- I need him them to know.
- Please no.
- No... more... lies.
James...
James.
He wasn't your father...
son.
What are you?
- I didn't mean it. I didn't.
- Yes, you did.
He deserved it. And
you gave it to him.
We're brothers, Jimmy.
You realise that?
Brothers protect each other.
You have to be hard now.
Hard enough they
can't ever touch us.
- I want to go home.
- We can't.
We stick together no matter what.
And take care of anyone
who gets in our way.
Can you do that, little brother?
They're coming. Can you run? Okay.
Keep on running. Don't look back.
Enough. Enough.
Stand down, soldier.
Victor.
Stand down.
No.
Ready.
Aim.
Wake me when it's over.
Fire.
My name is Major William Stryker.
You've been charged with
killing a senior officer.
Is that correct?
Apparently we have some
issues with authority.
Just keep a lid on it.
Sir.
The warden tells me that your
sentence was carried out...
by a firing squad at 1000 hours.
- How'd that go?
- It tickled.
You boys tired of running?
Tired of denying
your... true nature?
- What do you care?
- Oh, I care...
I care cause I know how
special you are...
how valuable.
Look.
You can stay here, locked
up like freaks of nature...
or you can join me.
I'm putting together
a special team...
with special privileges.
Now tell me...
How would you like to
really serve your country?
I love this weapon more than
anything in the whole wide world.
- You wanna know why?
- No.
It's memorable.
Sure, it's a little bulky, to
have to get 'em on a plane.
You whip out a couple of swords...
at your ex-girlfriend's wedding...
they will never, ever forget it.
That's funny, Wade.
I think you confused me with
someone who gives a shit.
Right, it is...
it's probably not as intimidating
as having a gun or...
bone claws or the fingernails
of a bag lady...
- Manicure?
- Victor... easy.
Fred got a new tattoo.
I'm concerned.
Oh geez, Fred, you just
met her last night.
- I love her.
- You love her after one night?
She's a gymnast.
Bradley, take her down.
Are you gonna puke?
If we were meant to fly,
we'd have grown wings.
Oh, don't worry man. See, more
people die driving than flying.
How about from impaling?
Hey, be nice. Or be your
approximation of nice.
Would you like a bucket?
Gentlemen, wheels down
in Lagos in five.
- Why are we here?
- All in good time. Zero...
Intruder.
Man your weapons.
Having fun yet?
- Fred...
- The tank?
- Tank.
- Yeah, I got that.
Great.
Stuck in an elevator with five
guys on a high protein diet.
- Oh Wade.
- Dreams really do come true.
Would you just shut
it. You're up next.
Thank you, sir. You
look very nice today.
It's the green.
Brings out the seriousness
in your eyes.
Oh my God, do you
ever shut up, pal?
No, not when I'm awake.
Bradley? Top floor, please.
Cover the elevator. The elevator.
Time to go to work.
Okay.
People are dead.
If you haven't that
mouth on you, Wade...
you'd be the perfect soldier.
I wouldn't do that if
I were you, brother.
Take the diamonds, they're yours.
I don't want your diamonds.
I want this.
That? That is nothing. A souvenir.
Where did you find it?
I want the source.
A small village, far inland,
three days from here.
Tell him that this rock is more
valuable to me than his life.
Ask him where he found it.
He says it came from the sky.
He's telling the truth.
You don't know their
language, Logan.
It's a meteor fragment.
I know what it is.
I'm asking him where he found it.
Sir, base wants to
know our location.
Shut him down.
Tell him everyone here will die...
unless he tells me where
he found the rock.
- He said that is sacred.
- Okay, fine.
Victor...
Victor.
Don't even think about it.
We didn't sign up for this.
Put him down.
What are you doing?
We finally got a good
thing going here.
Don't you screw this up.
Enough, it's enough.
We've done enough.
Who do you think you are?
This is what we do.
Maybe you'd rather be
rotting in a hole somewhere
till they figure out a way
to do it to us, is that it?
I'm done.
You coming?
Jimmy.
We can't just let you walk away.
Why are you up so early?
Come here.
See you baby.
Hey.
Oh, that's nice. Yeah.
No. Come on.
Hey, what do you do?
You turn off the light,
you win a prize.
- Two tries for a buck.
- Come on, I wanna do it.
That's obvious.
That's two.
- That's a stupid trick.
- It's not a trick, man.
C'mon. Freak.
Bye.
Show's over.
I said, show's over.
The show is never
over for us, Bradley.
- Victor.
- Aren't you gonna invite me in?
Yeah, come on in.
You know, I've never
said anything...
to anyone... about what happened.
I'm living a totally
different life now, but.
No need to bring up the past.
You know,
I always thought it would be
Wade coming knocking at my door.
Well, Wade's gone.
I'm not afraid of you, Victor.
I'm not afraid to die.
How do you know? You've
never tried it before.
Was it the wars?
- Which one?
- All of 'em.
Tell me.
It's just a scratch.
Looks like we're gonna need
new sheets again, baby.
Yeah...
Who the hell is this?
It smells like government.
My God. Haven't aged a day.
Clean living.
You remember Agent Zero.
Still shooting first and
asking questions later?
You still chewing
those cheap cigars?
Boys, please. I
have a job for you.
- I already have a job.
- Lumberjack.
- Eighteen grand a year?
- Eighteen five.
Plus I haven't had to
kill anyone in a while.
- Start to miss it?
- Yeah, right now I am.
Zero, back to the car.
Attaboy.
You know, I'm not proud about the
way things ended between us.
Conversation's over.
Play the little house on
the prairie with a...
a school teacher.
That's just isn't you, Logan.
And you would know, huh?
I would.
What do you want, Stryker?
Bradley was killed three days ago.
Wade, before that.
I believe that someone is
hunting down our old team.
Anyone else?
As far as I know, Victor is safe.
Whoever it is, he's had
names, addresses...
I can take care of myself.
This is not about you, Logan.
Your country needs you.
I'm Canadian.
I know you, Logan. I
know who you are.
What's wrong?
Stryker came by today.
Don't worry, I said no.
Why is he bothering you
after all these years?
Because I'm the best
there is at what I do.
And what I do best
isn't very nice.
You're not an animal, Logan.
What you have is a gift.
A gift?
You can return a gift.
Come on, fellas.
- Stay in the car.
- I'm just gonna ask nicely.
Mind letting us go by?
You're in some kind of
a hurry there, pal?
Are ya?
Just move your truck
so we can go by...
Trying to have a
conversation there, right.
If you start something...
you'd better be
ready to finish it.
Hey guys, take it easy.
Calm down.
Your boyfriend's got a big mouth.
I know.
Big temper too, so
please, let us pass.
Thank you.
How did you do that?
You know, power of
persuasion is a gift.
I see, do you... have
those powers over me?
Well, you didn't stay
in the car, did you?
Why is the moon so lonely?
Why?
Because she used to have a lover.
- You tell this to the kids?
- No.
His name was Kuekuatsheu...
and they lived in the
spirit world together.
- Ah, it's a true story.
- Right.
And every night, they would
wander the skies together.
But... one of the other
spirits was jealous.
Trickster, one of the
moons from South,
so he told Kuekuatsheu that the
moon had asked for flowers.
He told him to come
to our world...
and pick up some wild roses...
But Kuekuatsheu didn't know...
that once you leave
the spirit world...
you can never go back.
And every night, he
looks up in the sky...
and sees the moon
and howls her name.
But...
he can never touch her again.
Koo-koo-Kachooka got screwed.
Kuekuatsheu.
Means the Wolverine.
What you're doing, Logan?
Kayla.
You're not from
around here, are you?
What gave me away?
You got insurance on this place?
Insurance?
No.
Too bad.
Victor.
Well, well, well... Look
what the cat dragged in.
Guys, whatever this
is, take it outside.
- Why?
You don't call, you don't write.
How else am I supposed
to get your attention?
I hate to say it, Jimmy.
But, frankly, I'm a
little disappointed.
Stay down.
Tell me something,
Jimmy, was she worth it?
When are you gonna figure it out?
We're not like them.
I... am nothing like you.
Sure you are.
You just don't know it yet.
What do we got?
Bar fight. Multiple knife wounds.
What? Is this a joke?
The guy's fine.
Where is he?
I said where is he.
I don't know who he is.
I can help you.
Six years I've been here.
No one knew me and
then you show up.
- And the next day, she's dead.
- I tried to warn you.
Why don't you tell
me it was Victor?
I didn't know.
I swear on my son's
life. I didn't...
Victor's appetites were
becoming too public.
I had to lock him up. He
thought I'd betrayed him.
Went AWOL.
He said he was coming
after all of us.
You didn't come to warn me.
You came to save your own ass.
So what's your plan, captain?
You can't beat him, Logan,
you know you can't.
I'm gonna find him and kill him.
I can give you the
tools to defeat him.
- So we can still save the others.
- You mean save yourself, right?
I promise you two things:
You'll suffer more pain than
any other man can endure,
but you'll have your revenge.
If I come with you,
I'm coming for blood.
No law, no code of conduct.
You point me in the
right direction
and you get the
hell out of my way.
When it starts,
whatever the reason is
that you're doing this,
focus on that. Maybe it will help.
Trust me, I've been through worse.
No, you haven't.
We're ready.
We're gonna make you
indestructible.
But first, we're gonna
have to destroy you.
Remember what we were
looking for in Africa?
I remember.
Well, I found it.
It helped us create a...
metal compound so strong
that you will be able to
withstand virtually anything.
It's called Adamantium.
I can't put Victor
down myself, Logan.
To kill him, you're gonna have
to embrace the other side.
Become the animal.
Let's do this.
I almost forgot.
I want new ones.
What do you want them to say?
Wolverine.
Generals. Welcome.
General Munson.
Today, we're gonna
witness medical history.
create Weapon X.
X?
Roman numeral, Ten.
We are about to begin bonding
Adamantium to Weapon X's skeleton.
Let's begin.
- We're brothers, Jimmy.
- Logan.
Body temperature is
1-0-8 and rising.
Why is he thrashing like
that? Why isn't he sedated?
He feels pain, just
like the rest of us.
Anaesthesia won't work on him.
- That's why he had to volunteer.
- Heart rate 190.
195.
- Will he survive this?
- I don't know.
200.
Son.
Heartbeat's well beyond maximum.
- Blood pressure?
- 260 over 180 and rising.
He can make it, he can make it.
Victor.
I love you.
You're not an animal, Logan.
It means... the Wolverine.
Well, I guess he can die.
Come on, old friend. Come back.
Heart rate rising.
Adamantium reservoir is depleted.
No rejection. Procedure completed.
We did it.
We take him to the island?
The island? No.
The bonding works.
We use his DNA for the XI.
Erase his memory.
I think he heard you.
Lockdown.
Hunt him down. Take his head off.
Travis.
I think there is a
naked man in the barn.
Yep.
Son...
What in hell are you doing?
- It's cold.
- Cold?
- You got no clothes on.
- Yeah.
You're not onto drugs, are you?
No.
You just had a rough night.
Yeah, you could say that.
Come on up the house.
Some of my son's old clothes
will probably fit you.
Here, cover it up with that.
I don't want to give an
old lady a heart attack.
You're alright in there?
Yeah, I'm fine.
Supper's on the table.
I... Yeah, I'll be
there in a minute.
I swear I'm gonna pay for it.
Set it down over there.
Come and sit down, son.
I can't thank you both
enough... for everything.
It wouldn't have been decent to
leave you out there to freeze.
- Decent...
- What?
Nothing, I'm just not
really used to that word.
That's a nice chopper
you've got out there.
You know motorcycle?
Oh Lord, here we go.
My favourite is a '48 Panhead.
I bought one new off the line.
I think you're a little
young for that, son.
You must be exhausted. You
get a good night's sleep.
In the barn.
Nothing you can break out there.
- Why is the moon so lonely?
- Why?
Because she used to have a lover.
He can never touch her again.
You sleep ok?
Yeah.
You look like a man
fixing to do a bad thing.
You know what happens to
many looking for blood?
- What?
- They find it.
- We all got a choice, son.
- Yeah, mine got taken.
Bullshit.
This was my son's jacket.
Try it on.
- Thank you.
- Yep...
You wanna take my bike for a
spin, test the suspension.
'64, huh?
Man, you're heavy.
Yeah, I put on a little
weight recently.
Good morning.
Oh, it fits you beautifully.
I brought you some...
Weapon X is in the barn. He
just murdered two civilians.
Blow him to bits. Let's see
if he can survive that.
Come and get me.
Blow his brains all over the road.
Damn.
Alpha One, do not lose him.
Alpha 2, target's coming to you.
Pull up.
Zero?
Zero, come in.
Zero.
Zero, is Logan dead?
I don't know, I'm down.
Zero, come in.
You tried to kill me.
Logan?
Where is Victor?
Come back to base.
I'll explain everything, we'll
take Victor down together.
Wrong answer.
After I've killed Victor,
I'm coming for you.
Logan, listen to me.
If you go down this road, you're
not gonna like what you find.
You wanted the animal, Colonel?
You got it.
Those were good people back there.
Innocent people.
It's funny how good innocent
people tend to die around you.
Zero never stood a chance.
The only thing that'll take him
down is an Adamantium bullet.
This facility is
compromised. Prep transport.
Colonel, this is turning
into a disaster.
- Don't worry, we'll stop him.
- Really?
You've just spent half
a billion dollars...
making him indestructible.
- Sir?
- Yes.
The young mutant you've been
looking for, we found him.
General, Logan isn't the
only piece in this puzzle.
I need to evacuate this facility.
Please, go back to Washington.
We've got work to do.
You talk, el habla?
Somebody translate?
Summers?
Sit up and take off those glasses.
I have a headache.
Then you can wear them in
detention after school
while you add up this
conjugation 100 times.
- Somebody else?
- He talks.
Thank you, he talks. El habla.
- You sure it was Victor?
- Yeah.
Damn.
I'm sorry, mate.
What the hell happened
to him after I left?
He got worse.
He felt like you abandoned him.
Hell, we all do.
But Victor, he had to prove
you he was better than you.
Hunting and killing everything's
he was pointing at.
Quit a few months later myself,
couldn't take rounding them up.
- Rounding who up?
- Leave it alone.
Rounding who up, John?
Hey. God damn it, John.
We hunted our own kind, Logan.
There's a special place in
hell for the things we did.
Mutants?
Why?
Stryker'd say we would
be making a difference.
Protecting people
from the bad ones.
How are you gonna take
Victor down, Logan?
Remember that stuff in Africa?
Yeah, I remember
Africa, what about it?
Damn.
What'd they do to you?
Don't ask.
Listen, Zero said something
about an island.
Does that mean anything to you?
Nope.
But maybe Dukes knows.
- Him and Zero were real tight.
- Fred Dukes?
- Where is he?
- He's here.
- Well, let's go talk to him.
- Hold on.
He don't get in until around four.
But I gotta warn you...
he developed a bit
of eating disorder.
We all got our coping mechanisms.
I'm trying to whoop
him back into shape.
Whatever you do, don't
mention his weight.
Come on, Fred, if you want to get
into shape, you gotta move, man.
I told him he got to move.
Fred Dukes? Trapped inside that
creature? That ain't Fred Dukes.
Hey, be nice.
Hey, Fat, Fred.
See, I remember that girl when
she's got 85 pounds, huh.
Oh that's funny. You're
still so funny, Logan.
You know where Victor is?
No idea.
What's the island, slim?
Don't let the door hit you
on the way out, Logan.
Listen, I ain't gonna leave until
you tell me where Victor is.
Come on, Bob. For old
times' sake, huh?
Did you just call me...
Blob?
No, but...
I told you not to
mention his weight.
Why did you call him Blob?
I didn't call him
Blob, I said Bob.
Goddamn it.
I got an idea.
- This is your idea of an idea?
- Trying to help you out, Logan.
Dukes don't like you that
much, and you know it.
The feeling is mutual.
Use those gloves, man, dance
with him a little bit.
Allow him to let his
anger out on you.
I figure if you do that...
he might tell you
everything you wanna know.
Come on, man, look at him.
Big old ass coming out of
the front of his shirt.
Jesus, he's gonna have a
coronary for Christ's sake.
Is there even a
stretcher big enough...
to take this guy out of here?
It ain't him I'm worried about
getting out on a stretcher.
- You're an asshole.
- Come on, Logan.
Whoop his ass.
- If you want.
- Dance with him Fred.
What's that suppose to do?
You wanna dance with me?
Oh. Oh, that feels good.
Hey, guess what?
See, he's gonna talk, man.
You got him right
where you want him.
Whose side are you on anyway?
Come on now, lambchop.
Now, where is Victor?
A little dark for sunglasses,
don't you think?
Please don't. Please.
Don't, please.
Victor.
Hey. Where's Victor?
Victor's... with Stryker
on... on the island...
they... they run it together.
What... what?
Victor's been with Stryker?
Yeah.
You didn't know that?
All that's left now is Logan, I...
trust you can handle that.
I did before, didn't I?
Oh yes, you did that.
Our deal... it still
applies, right?
Of course.
Now pack him and tag him, Captain.
What's the island?
It's where... Striker takes
them after Victor's caught 'em.
Wait, wait... what? Takes who?
Mutants.
The rumour is that Stryker's
doing experiments on them there.
Well, you never wondered
what happened to them?
I tried not to.
They killed her...
so I'd let them put
Adamantium in me.
They killed her for a
goddamn experiment.
Where is it?
Logan, Stryker kept
it real secret.
But...
- A prisoner escaped there once.
- Who?
His name is Remy LeBeau.
He was a street hustler
from New Orleans.
The guards at the prison
called him Gambit
because he kept taking all
their money at poker...
that's all I know.
What's Stryker up to Fred,
what's the end game?
He's taking their powers,
trying to combine them somehow.
It's all I know, Logan.
It's all I know.
If I had to come back here,
I'm gonna take your head off.
I'm coming with you, Logan.
There's no redemption
where I'm going.
I ain't asking.
There's our dude.
That's cool.
But I'm going to go and
cover the back if he runs.
I'm not having a fight with him.
- Yeah right.
- What?
I am having fights with everybody?
Don't dogs kill cats?
Just go cover the back, will ya?
Are you Remy LeBeau?
Do I owe you money?
No.
Then Remy LeBeau I am.
Large blind is 100, and
the small blind's 50.
May I deal you in?
Now what can I get for 17 bucks?
17 dollars?
A cab ride home, perhaps.
You're my brother's
new babysitter, John?
I ain't Bradley, Victor.
And your creepy black
coat don't scare me.
Really?
It worked on Dukes.
Shouldn't had done that, because
now I'm gonna kill you...
before Logan gets the chance.
So what brings you to
our fair city, sir?
Victor Creed.
And who's that?
The man I'm gonna kill.
He works for a man named
Stryker on, on an island.
- I just need to know where it is.
- Why would you think I know that?
Well, because I know
who you are, Gambit.
You are the guy who escaped...
and you are the guy who's
gonna take me back there.
You know, John...
There's something I always
wanted to tell you.
You're predictable.
I can feel your spine, Johnny Boy.
That's funny. I never
knew you had one.
Those are mighty nice tags
you have on there, sir.
The men who took me wore
tags just like 'em.
Hey, now Bob, you listen to me...
Two years I was rotting
in that hell...
and I'm never going back.
Oh, shiny.
Tell me something, Jimmy.
Do you even know how to kill me?
I'm gonna cut your
goddamn head off.
See if that works.
You're getting slow, old man.
Son of a bitch.
You're gonna die for
what you did to her.
Victor.
That's a nice stick.
Shithead. Here's the deal.
See, you're gonna take me to this
island, where I can kill Creed,
Stryker, pretty much everyone
you hate in this world.
Do you understand?
You really gonna kill 'em.
As long as you stay
out of my way, yeah.
Colonel.
General?
Is this Weapon XI?
All their strenghts but
none of their weaknesses.
You really hate them, don't you?
No, I don't hate them.
After 20 years of
working with them...
I just know what they can do.
If we win this war
before it starts...
it'll save countless
lives in the process.
Preemptive action is the
only action here, General.
The days of our country sitting
on the sidelines are over.
We need to take the
fight to the enemy...
before they take the fight to us.
- I admire your passion, I do.
- Thank you.
But this is as far as it goes.
Weapon X was a... a hickup.
We know about your son, Bill.
We know he's a mutant.
And we know he killed your wife.
You shouldn't have
kept that from us.
That...
That has nothing to
do with my work.
Bullshit.
You're too close to this.
I'm sure you know it.
You're right. I won't lie to you.
My son did bring the
problem home for me.
But I took an oath...
to protect the American people
from every threat,
both foreign
and domestic.
- You don't like flying, huh?
- I'm fine.
Just concentrate on
what you're doing.
You sure? You got a bit of
sweat on your brow there.
Very funny, just keep
your eyes on the...
On the what? Clouds?
We're jumping up and down
like a freaking yoyo here.
Where did you get
this thing anyway?
Oh, this is my baby,
I won her in a game.
- Jacks over fives.
- Great.
Relax. We're almost there.
There it is. The island.
Three Mile Island.
Hiding in plain sight.
No one's gonna snoop
around a nuclear reactor.
They think it's gonna
turn them into freaks.
Like you?
Right.
All right, you ready?
Because it's now or
never. Let's go.
About time.
Hey, if it's make you
feel any better...
this is really gonna hurt.
Well yeah, it kind
of does actually.
Good luck.
Likewise.
Oh shit.
How are you doing?
Is everything alright?
- Is he ready yet?
- A few more hours.
And he will respond
to my commands?
Absolutely.
Logan.
Welcome back to the war.
Before I gut you,
I wanna know why.
I needed your powers for the pool.
For the what?
A mutant killer. The dead pool.
Years of searching, to find...
finding the right powers...
that can coexist in one body
without ripping it apart.
My son was the first
piece of the puzzle.
Logan, you were the last.
You made Weapon XI possible.
I...
I asked you to help but...
you said you wanted
the quiet life.
Well...
I've learned that
nothing motivates...
the men in your
family like revenge.
Who are you?
Oh she's a real old friend.
Do you really think we'd
just let you walk away?
You are a dangerous man.
I like to keep an eye
on dangerous men.
Tell him about the day you died.
They gave me a shot of
hydrochloride thiazide.
It reduces the heart
rate so low...
it appears you flatline.
Don't be angry with her.
Real credit... to your species.
Did you know that her sister...
has diamond-hard skin?
Kayla's mutation
is tacto-hypnosis.
She can influence people as
long as she touches them.
Quite a useful tool
in the seduction.
It was never real, my friend.
It was real for me.
I told you if you came
down this road...
you wouldn't like
what you'd found.
That story you told me...
about man who gets
flowers for the moon...
I had it backwards.
I thought you were the moon
and I was your Wolverine.
But you were the
Trickster, aren't you?
I am just the fool
that got played.
The worst part of this
is I should have known.
But I ignored my instincts.
I ignored what I really am.
Well, that will
never happen again.
- Colonel.
- Not now, Kayla.
I have done everything
you've asked.
My sister...
You said that if I help
you, you'd let her go.
Kayla, it's not as simple as that.
Her mutation is unique.
Quite beautiful.
We just need a little more time
to analyse it, that's all.
You let him go?
- Victor, please.
- You can't let him go.
- You can't beat him, Victor.
- Give me the Adamantium.
- Tests came out...
- We had a deal.
You would never survive
the operation.
I can take anything he can.
No, you can't.
You are my favourite
soldier, Victor.
Be patient, time will come.
He's using us.
How about this time,
you die for real?
Let me go.
Your little mind game
don't work on me.
Victor.
Feels good, doesn't it?
All that rage...
Do it.
Logan.
You're not an animal.
Oh yes, you are.
Do it.
Finish it.
Logan?
My sister.
They have my sister.
Please, I didn't trick
you into loving me.
It was real for me too.
Please, I'm so sorry.
They have my sister.
Where is she?
Activate Weapon XI.
The bonding process is incomplete.
Just do it. Now.
Are you okay? Come on.
Okay...
Perfect.
Kayla, get these kids out of here.
Logan...
Find another way out.
Come on, let's go.
Wade, is that you?
I guess Stryker finally figured
out how to shut you up.
Wade...
You don't have to do this.
Alright, maybe you do.
Shoot on sight.
I can help. Point me at 'em.
Go.
Go. Now.
Did I get them?
Yeah.
- Let's go.
- I can't go.
Kayla, come on.
I have to stay here.
You take them.
Go.
Go left.
Left.
- What?
- We go left.
- You can't see.
- Trust me.
C'mon Bob. Let's see
your dance up here.
Nobody kills you but me.
Back-to-back.
- I got him.
- Oh no, you don't.
Stop.
- This can't be the way.
- This is the way.
- How do you know?
- I just know.
Come on.
Adamantium bullets.
Let's see him heal with a few of
these through his thick skull.
You can't stop him.
Even with that.
He'll heal.
His brain may heal.
But his memories won't grow back.
This doesn't change anything
between us, Victor.
We're done.
We can never be done, Jimmy.
We're brothers.
Brothers look out for each other.
- You miss me?
- Jesus...
You know, when you said you
were gonna kill everyone...
I thought you may just've
been exaggerating.
Yeah...
Do I look like a man
who exaggerates?
You're welcome.
Logan.
These kids trying to
get off the island.
- Split up. Go.
- I'm on it.
Kayla.
I love you.
No...
I'm so cold.
Listen to me, I'm gonna
get you outta here.
You understand?
Let's go easy, nice and easy.
That's it.
I'm gonna get you out.
Logan.
I should make you
pull the trigger.
But that would make us
no better than you.
Throw the gun away.
Turn around. Walk until
your feet bleed.
And then keep walking.
It'll be all right, Scott.
My name is Charles Xavier.
I'm a mutant, like you.
- I can hear your thoughts.
- Yes. And I can hear yours.
You're safe now.
Come. We have to go.
The kids are safe.
What the hell happened?
- Who are you?
- What do you mean, who am I?
I'm the guy who brought you
here. Now we gotta go.
Where the hell am I?
Listen to me, I am a friend.
I'm a friend.
What's my name?
What's my name.
Your name is Logan.
You need to trust
me. We have to go.
Follow me.
Now.
Do you know her?
No.
These dudes are not gonna like
what you've done in this place.
We really need to go.
I'll find my own way.
Good luck.
Colonel Stryker?
- Colonel William Stryker?
- Yes.
You're wanted for questioning...
in connection of the
death of General Munson.
Sir.